<rss version="2.0"><channel><item><title>2016-02-13 - Compliment on Police Officer of New Territories North Region</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 

I am writing to show my appreciation to a Police officer who was on duty to handle a domestic discord case of my family.  He patiently helped alleviate the resentment between my sister and mother by making use of his eloquence. 

The dispute between my sister and mother was about whether my sister should pay for family expenses.  The officer movingly told a story as an evidence in order to persuade them to eliminate their biases, which was about paying his parents for family expenses and thus he could only had cup noodles for lunch for a week.  Anyway, now we are back to harmony.  To thank his crucial aid, I want to make use of this letter to honor his impressive contribution.  Thank you for your attention. 
                                                                      
Yours faithfully,
Ma

Note : Officer praised in this letter is Sergeant 1975 YEUNG Ming-ki of Platoon 3 Emergency Unit, New Territories North Region</content></item><item><title>2016-02-14 – Compliment on Police Officer of Western Division</title><content>Special thanks to the Police officers for kindly locating my Octopus card which I've accidentally lost at the park.  I was very grateful for their kindness for trying so hard to locate me and return the card to me.  I must say that they are very efficient and they represented Hong Kong Police so well!!!!!

Ms. ZEE

Note : Officers praised in this letter are Sergeant 34877 WONG Man-dick, PC 16643 CHU Wan-pang and PC 18411 PANG Chun-yin of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Western Division</content></item><item><title>2016-02-13 - Compliment on Police Officer of Tseung Kwan O Division</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam,

I write to express my sincere gratitude and appreciation to three Police officers for their professional attitude and proactive assistance provided regarding a noise complaint case lodged against my neighbour.

Upon my report to the Police (via calling 999) about suspected noise nuisance around midnight on 9th February 2016, the officers paid visit to my residence quickly and conducted thorough and effective investigation of the case, followed by prompt action (that was, to friendly remind the complained flat not to play musical instruments after 11:00 p.m. based on the Cap.400 regulations on noise nuisance).  It was a very impressive experience as they communicated with all stakeholders and were also willing to solve the case by paying extra effort (that was, to communicate with us before, during and also after the case).

The case was eventually solved to everyone’s satisfaction after their practical communication with my neighbour.  My family was of no doubt contented, if not marveled, by their comprehensive delivery of Police service.  It is indeed fair to comment that the team of three officers had not only solved a minor residence case but also promoted a positive image of the Police to the general public.  We have taken the privilege to share such pleasing experience to many of our friends and fellows.

To encourage and enhance the excellent performance of the Police Force, it will be most grateful if your relevant officers would thus receive relevant commendations for their silent yet industrious work done, which is believed to be seen across many cases including mine.  Thanks to your wise management and team work, I am confident that there will be more appreciation reports from citizens in near future.

Yours faithfully
Mr. LO

Note : One of the officers praised in this letter is PC 859 CHIN Siu-sun of Patrol Sub-unit 3, Tseung Kwan O Division.</content></item><item><title>2016-02-07 – Compliment on Police Officer of Railway District</title><content>I clumsily left my luggage in a taxi.  Rushing to catch a flight leaving in 3 hours, I tried frantically to contact the taxi company.  They were not responsive for about an hour.  Failing which I went to the police post at IFC to make a report.  Very quickly, the police officers on duty offered a solution.  They were kind, efficient, and understanding.  Their helpfulness and experience were vital in locating the taxi owner and eventually the driver.  By this time there was a change in the reporting officers who were equally brilliant. 

I managed to meet the driver and eventually collected my luggage.  Everything was in tact and I rushed to the airport.  Though I missed my flight and had to be on standby for the next 5 hours, the entire experience made me appreciate what the HK Police can do for HK.

Officer LUK followed up with a call and that was super!  I am now enjoying my time with my family for the Lunar New Year.  I would like to sincerely thank the officers for their excellent service and effective assistance.  Finally, wishing them a prosperous and wonderful start to the Lunar New Year.

Mr. LAI

Note : Two of the officers praised in this letter are SPC 47759 LEUNG Kin-kwok and PC 1681 LUK Tat-hung of Lantau Airport Railway, Railway District</content></item><item><title>2016-02-06 – Compliment on Police Officer of New Territories South Region</title><content>On 3 February 2016, after I reported that there was an excessive and dangerous amount of debris on the road, the officer immediately went to the site and expediently removed the debris, while keeping me updated. The officer had the utmost professionalism and efficiency.   

Ms. CHAN

Note : Officer praised in this letter is PC 8174 TO Yiu-ting of Enforcement and Control Division (Road Work Inspection Team 5), Territories South Road Management Office, Territories South Region</content></item><item><title>2016-02-04 - Compliment on Police Officers of Western Division</title><content>Dear Sir,

I am writing to express my sincere thanks for your kindness help.  I am a HKU student who lost my Mac book in university and called the Police this month.  The Police officers came to school soon and helped me find the clues patiently.  They are so professional, kind and friendly.  With the help of Police, I found my laptop in the school office finally.  Maybe this is just a small case to you, but it is really an important thing to me! 

With thanks again and best wishes to you and your colleagues! .

Yours,
Miss Zhu

Note : the officers praised in this letter are SGT 58101 YUEN Chun-yue, SPC 49741 LAI Chiu-tat and PC 19288 WONG Hon-hin of Patrol Sub-unit 3, Western Division</content></item><item><title>2016-02-01 - Compliment on Police Officers of Kwun Tong District</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I would like to take this opportunity to express my gratitude to TKO Police Station and two police officers for their kind assistance in investigating my case.

The officers Mr. Tang and Mr. Chan demonstrated patience, excellent knowledge and professionalism in the investigation process.  I appreciate them totally!

Thank You!

Ms Leung

Note : the officers praised in this letter are SGT 49413 CHAN Wai-yuen and PC 12125 TANG Kai-him of District Investigation Team 7, Kwun Tong District</content></item><item><title>2016-02-01 - Compliment on Police Officer of Wanchai Division</title><content>I reported loss of my wallet today.  During the reporting period, police officer is very kind, trying to help me to contact the driver.  Afterwards he contacted the driver and asked me to contact him directly to get back the wallet.  Before I met the taxi driver, he called me again to check the status, and asked me to tell him whether everything is fine after getting the wallet.  I called back to appreciate his attitude and patient.  He is very efficient. 

Mr. Sinn 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 53928 Yu Wing-ho of Patrol Sub-unit 3, Wanchai Division</content></item><item><title>2016-01-27 - Compliment on Police Officer of Shatin District</title><content>I am writing to express my utmost gratitude for the valiant efforts of Police officers, especially officer James for personally handling my case and answering all my queries patiently although my Chinese was really bad.  Also as I am a Singaporean who got my phone stolen overseas, I had lost hope in retrieving the phone as chances to detect these cases were low.  But I was surprised when James went out of his way and contacted me 3 days after I filed my report, saying that they had captured the thief and retrieved my phone. 

I would also like to commend the Hong Kong Police on their competency in this matter. 

Mr. Hoon

Note : one of the officers praised in this letter is PC 13943 CHIM Hok-in, James of District Investigation Team 6, Shatin District</content></item><item><title>2016-01-26 - Compliment on Police Officer of Tin Shui Wai Division</title><content>I travelled on a bus going from Guangzhou to Hong Kong on 2016-01-21, and crossed from the Mainland to Hong Kong at the Shenzhen Bayport Terminal.  I somehow lost my mobile phone on the way to Hong Kong, but didn't discover it until almost noon when someone answered my phone and said the phone would be returned to the Shenzhen Bayport Police Station on the Hong Kong side.  I had a round trip ticket and returned to Shenzhen Bayport at around 1700 hours and then went to the Police Station.  I was assisted by Police officers who were both very professional and efficient in tracking my phone, which was turned in to the station at about 1730 hours by a bus driver.  I am extremely grateful to both officer PC 9735 and WPC 14926 for their efforts to help me recover my phone.

Ms Molly

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 9735 CHIN Kwok-man and WPC 14926 CHAN Pui-sin of Shenzhen Bay Port, Tin Shui Wai Division</content></item><item><title>2016-01-25 – Compliment on Police Officer of Cheung Chau Division</title><content>We would like to thank you very much for the Police officers’ efforts to rescue our Grey African parrot safely and take great care of him. 

Thanks to officers’ kind help, our bird could escape from the cold weather in your great care.  We could tell that he was so much relieved when we came for him at the Police station, comparing with the photo taken at the time that he was discovered on the street (a photo of him appeared scared and tired from Peng Chau residents' Facebook).  The Police officer’s assistance was more than mere responsibility, but warm and heartfelt help to us citizens.

We could not imagine what harm would had come to him without your rescue and protection.  We are especially grateful for your identification on the owner by bird ring and birthday certificate.  The officers’ thoughtfulness and professionalism are definitely worthy of our respect.

It is great to know that we are in very good hands with Hong Kong Police in service!

Many thanks again and best regards,

Ms Chan and Mr Ie

Note : one of the officers praised in this letter is PC 49977 HO Wai-yip of Patrol Sub-unit 3, Cheung Chau Division</content></item><item><title>2016-01-23 - Compliment on Police Officer of Aberdeen Division</title><content>Dear Sir, 

This is just a thank you note as the Police officer has been very diligent and helpful when handling our complaint for noise pollution. 

Thanks a lot!  Your support was much appreciated! 

Alexandra 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 15188 NG Ka-fai of Patrol Sub-unt 2, Aberdeen Division</content></item><item><title>2016-01-13 – Compliment on Police Officers of Chai Wan District</title><content>I accidentally left my mobile phone on green minibus when I got off near Fung Yip Street, Chai Wan and only realized after the minibus drove away.  I tried to chase the minibus until the next stop but in vain as it left before I reached the stop. 

Noticed a police officer on motorcycle at intersection of Fu Hong Street &amp; Siu Sai Wan Road as I ran after minibus and told him what happened, he quickly chased the minibus to its next stop at Island Resort Mall and was able to tell the minibus driver about my phone.  I was eventually able to recover my mobile phone, thanks to the helpful police officer.

Unfortunately, I forgot to get his details, although I did thank him verbally.

Regards,
Dr. Chan</content></item><item><title>2016-01-13 - Compliment of Police Officer of Western Division</title><content>I would like to take this opportunity to express my gratitude to police officers for helping out to search for my dad who had run out in the afternoon from home.  As my dad got Alzheimer, he ran away in the afternoon without informing any of us.  The police officers were very helpful and efficient in assisting in the searching process.  Really appreciate their assistance.

Ms. YAN

Note : the officer praised in this letter are Sergeant 49983 CHOI Chi-ping, PC 19270 KU Yat-hei and PC 16206 NG Sui-leung of Patrol Sub-unit 4 Western Division</content></item><item><title>2016-01-13 - Compliment of Police Officer of Kowloon East Region</title><content>Police officer Mr. Pang is very polite, gentle, smart, clever and courteous.  He handled my case carefully and in details.  He can take his heart to help us to check so many related things.  All his behavior can let us know his helpfulness and goodness. He always called us and kept in contact with us about the related process.  He gave us so many support and let us feel HK policeman can help us a lot during this time. Also, his team work is so far so good, every partner can follow this case so carefully and understood all the related details.

Mr. Pang is a so perfect policeman.  We hope your department can show his perfect performance to all the other police and do like him to help HK people in need.  God bless them forever!

Thank you very much for him and his team partners again and hope Mr. Pang will have a higher position to lead other partners to stay in HK Police to help HK in the future time.

Ms. WAN

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 1733 PANG Wai-wa of Regional Missing Person Unit, Kowloon East</content></item><item><title>2016-01-05 - Compliment on Police Officer of Emergency Unit Hong Kong Island</title><content>I was approaching No. 1 bus stop heading for the Happy Valley outside the China Overseas Building, Wan Chai and I was stopped by two police officers very politely in warm gesture and helpful manner because of the fire broke out incident on that day! Then I followed the way they showed me and I was there at the No. 1 bus stop; while I was waiting for the bus I have observed police officer PC 12610 whom stood right under the other bus stop did his best to help the elderly who came out from the taxi right in front of the site!  The elderly with companies that have difficulties to walk, PC 12610 approached them without hesitation and helped.  He has also drawn the attention of one female colleague and someone looked like a supervisor and they all helped to stop the traffic for moving the elderly and companies out of the site as soon as possible!

This scene at the site has been touching and I hope that this compliment can encourage police officers to know that they should be proud of helping people in the uniform of the Hong Kong Police Force!

These people of the above mentioned are not only the asset of your department and they are the assets of us Hong Kong Citizens too!

I would like to mention that the head of this group must be an excellent leader because from the officers whom I have first met at the scene they are all so professional and helpful !

Finally may I take the chance of wish all of you and family a very Happy New Year 2016 !

Sincerely yours,
LAM TZ

Note : one of the officer praised in this letter is PC 12610 WONG Ho-tak of Platoon 3, Emergency Unit Hong Kong Island</content></item><item><title>2016-01-04 - Compliment on Police Officer of Wan Chai Division</title><content>Greeting, I hope this link will note my appreciation to a police officer.  I brought hundreds of lost or found items to police station.  The police officer is very patient and polite when handling my case.  The best thing I felt is he kept asking me "Was I hungry?" Kept informing me of the expectation of how long it was going to take!!  He made me feel he is very easy-going and really keen to help and support!!! 

He truly makes the Hong Kong Police Force to be proud.  Thumbs up!!! 

Thank you!!
Mr. Chui

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 16674 YEUNG Chung-hin of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Wan Chai Division</content></item><item><title>2016-01-02 - Compliment on Police Officer of Railway District</title><content>I salute two police officers for the kindness, courtesy and immediate response to our concern on a baggage left inside a cab trunk when we were dropped off to our flight home to the Philippines.  Both officers were accommodating, friendly and helpful when I approached them.  They immediately located and contacted the driver and helped me get back my luggage.  In a span of 30 minutes, police officer retrieved my luggage and I was so happy to meet such amazing officers of the Hong Kong Police. 

As a frequent tourist of Hong Kong, (I visit Hong Kong at least once a year) it is very nice to know that I have someone to trust and turn to when trouble arises.  I recommend that these officers be commended and properly recognized as I have witnessed how they help tourists like me and my family far away from home when we need someone to help us.  Thank you again for a job well done and extending your hand beyond the call of duty.  I hope to see you soon when I visit Hong Kong again this 2016.  God Bless and sending love from the Philippines! 

Miss Angel

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 50964 Yau Kin-cheong and PC 34221 Tsai Yu-ping of Lantau Airport Railway, Railway District</content></item><item><title>2015-12-24 – Compliment on Police Officer of Kowloon City District</title><content>Dear Police Commissioner,

I am writing to praise the fine police work by Police Officer LAU. This is a relatively petty crime in which the total amount of fraud money involved was less than $30K HKD.  Nevertheless, Officer LAU, took the case seriously as it involved multiple victims. He spent much efforts to find the suspect. While this case did not result in a conviction, it was a happy ending for everyone involved. This outcome was not possible without the great efforts and diligent police works of Officer LAU. Moreover, since I often travel outside of HK, he had to contact me at least 10 times before we finally meet up to sign off on the case.  Each time, Officer LAU was very polite and accommodating.  

In short, I am thoroughly impressed by Officer LAU's fine attitude and professionalism throughout the case.  Please rely my regard and appreciation for his fine police works.

Thx
Mr. OU

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC1582 LAU Yuk-ming of District Investigation Team 3, Kowloon City District </content></item><item><title>2015-12-22 - Compliment on Police Officer of Traffic New Territories South Region</title><content>I am writing to express my gratitude and appreciation to the swift response by a police officer who is assisting me to investigate a hit and run case of my car. 

In Dec 2015 afternoon, I went to the Traffic New Territories South to report the case of my car was hit and run by other car at a carpark. Even though I understand there may be many other cases handling by the officer, he responded to my case and went to the carpark in early morning. As time is very important to my case since the CCTV record of the carpark might have been deleted after a certain period. Fortunately the CCTV has recorded down the parked area of my car. 

I appreciate and sincerely thank you for police officer’s effort and prompt response to my case.

Mr. CHUNG

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 10181 LAU Hei-yee of Accident Investigation Team 6, Traffic New Territories South Region</content></item><item><title>2015-12-21 - Compliment on Police Officer of Wan Chai District</title><content>In December, about a probable forgery of my identity for a loan application, police officer gave me a call this morning; and very kindly explained similar cases at length to assuage my worry about illegal employ of my identity. 

I am most grateful as officer Ms. WONG also informed her contact telephone number so that I may report if in the unlikely case.  

Ms. YAU

Note : the officer praised in this letter is WPC 4168 WONG Pui-pui of District Intelligence Section, Wan Chai District</content></item><item><title>2015-12-21 - Compliment on Police Officer of Castle Peak Division</title><content>I lost my Octopus Card at the Gold Coast Piazza in Dec 2015. I contacted the security guards of the shopping mall but was much frustrated by their in cooperation and unwillingness to assist me. I therefore contacted the Police, and a police officer took my case. I was much impressed by his efficiency. Within an hour, he checked the security video and drew me the number of my lost Octopus card which I used for car parking. I have only lost an Octopus card, but he was still very devoted to my case, updating me with his investigation through several phone calls within that hour. 
 
I highly appreciate and admire this officer. I am much astounded, yet very impressed, by his devotion and attitude. I highly appreciate the Hong Kong Police Force taking great attention and effort to each and every case. I am sure that the Hong Kong Police Force will continue to display this excellent efficiency in work and fight against crime for the citizens. Thank you very much. 
 
Yours sincerely,
Alan CHAN
 
Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 473 LI Wai-nok of Patrol Sub-unit 2 Castle Peak Division</content></item><item><title>2015-12-16 - Compliment of Police Officers of Mong Kok District</title><content>Dear Commissioner Lo,
 
This letter is to thank you for the time and effort of your police officers at Mongkok Police Station in a seemingly minor incident.  It is very reassuring that there are policemen dedicated to the safety of the people of Hong Kong.
 
I am to thank you for the support and service of the Hong Kong Police Force for searching my missing father.
 
My elderly 83-years-old father was reported missing when he went to restroom during lunch at a restaurant in Mongkok. We were waiting for him to return to finish his meal for over 2 hours. I became worried and called your fellow colleagues for assistance. After 6 o’clock, he eventually returned home safely as he had got on a bus by himself to a park hear home for whole afternoon but forgot to return to restaurant for our lunch.  I was so happy and relieved to know my father was safe home due to the efforts of the policemen after 6 hours.
 
Although I am not a resident in Hong Kong, I travel often to the city and now know the hospitality of the Hong Kong Police Force of which I am proud.
 
Most sincere regards,
FOK

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 7699 LEUNG Chun-ho, PC 2666 FONG Wai-kin, PC 18332 YIP Kwan-ki of Patrol Sub-units of Mong Kok District and PC 16773 KWONG Pui-lam of District Traffic Team, Mong Kok District</content></item><item><title>2015-12-10 - Compliment on Police Officer of Airport District</title><content>I left my laptop bag in a taxi on my way to Hong Kong International Airport.  Then, I reported the case to a police officer at the airport.  The officer on duty did a very good job by locating my lost laptop bag in a short time.

I appreciate the good work done by the officer.

Roy

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 33222 CHEUNG Yau-hong of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Airport District</content></item><item><title>2015-12-08 - Compliment on Police Officers of Lantau South Division</title><content>We are the owner of a premises at Tai O, Lantau and would like to write this letter showing our appreciation for the outstanding performance of Hong Kong Police officers.

We had a very pleasant experience with three Police officers whom we have found them very helpful in handling my repossession of the property from my tenant. 

Before moving back to U.K., we would like you to recognize these three excellent officers.  Thank you for your attention.
 
Yours sincerely,
Ms. STRACHAN 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 52422 KONG Kam-leung, PC 33440 CHEUNG Wai-kwan and PC 46954 LEUNG Chung-fong of Patrol Sub-unit 3, Lantau South Division</content></item><item><title>2015-12-05 - Compliment on Police Officers of Yaumatei Division</title><content>At the end of November, there were police officers helping us to control the traffic conditions near a music festival, which helped us to solve many traffic problems and made everything smooth there.  Besides, a police officer (PCA6263) gave a lot of advice and patience to advise people there to use the right way. 

I highly recommend what he did on that day despite the heavy workload and hot weather.  His concentration made my staff and my team delighted.  He is a hard working police officer who did a fabulous job.  Thank you very much for his support and his team.

Mr. CHAN

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PCA 6263 TSENG Kin-yung of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Yaumatei Division</content></item><item><title>2015-12-03 - Compliment of Police Officers of Wan Chai District</title><content>Dear Sir,

I and on behalf of my wife would like to thank the Hong Kong Police for their dedication and professionalism in investigating a case. 

This ordeal has taken a significant mental and physical toll on my wife.  We greatly appreciate the courtesy shown towards us from the involved police officers and their ongoing dedication to ensure justice is done for the involved families and investors who have lost significant sums of money as a result of dishonest practices. 

Best Regards
Mr. Cheng

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Inspector YIP Pak-lun, Sergeant 754 NG Ting-hong, PC 12509 CHIU Sik-sun of District Investigation Team 3, Wan Chai District</content></item><item><title>2015-12-03 - Compliment of Police Officersof Tin Shui Wai Division</title><content>I reported a lost of cellular phone case in Kingswood Richly Plaza.  I was interviewed by a Madam for all the details of my lost I phone 6s rose gold color, and she suggested me bringing back the cellphone package for recording the serial number in police's file, as she detailedly explained what would happen afterwards on the police side, such as matching on the system.

One hour later, I returned to the same police station with my cellphone package and intended to update the information in my record.  The same Madam told me that my dad was in the police station and asked me to give him a call.  At the same time, another male police officer who was sitting two counters next to her was holding my cellular phone and asked me if that was my phone.  So it was an old lady who picked up my phone on the floor inside the mall and she was returning it to the police station and coincidentally I was there at the same time. 

I am writing a compliment to the police officers for being attentive even though my report of loss cellphone was just a minor case.  I appreciate their help and wish that their attitude could be praised for their contribution to our community.  

Miss LEE</content></item><item><title>2015-12-02 - Compliment of Police Officers of Kowloon City Division</title><content>I am a teacher working in Thailand.  I was travelling in Hong Kong.  On the day in the evening, I took a taxi from Hotel to Shamshuipo, I was so careless that I left my luggage in the car, after that the taxi driver brought my luggage to Kowloon City police station.

Finally they reached my friends who stayed in Hotel.  Meanwhile, I went to Shamshuipo police station, a police officer there told me that all the police officers in Kowloon City police station were looking for me.

Thank you so much all the policemen in Kowloon City police station, when I got there, I found that all of them were working on my case, they called the hotel, they tried their best to reach me.

I believe that Hong Kong is a fantastic city because of that Hong Kong has such good police team always helping people!!  Best wishes to all police officers in Hong Kong.  Thank you, Kowloon City police station.  And thank you, that taxi driver even if I don't know your name! 

All of you make Hong Kong so AMAZING!!!!

Mr. Wei</content></item><item><title>2015-12-01 - Compliment of Police Officers of Tai Po District</title><content>Dear Sir,

I am writing to appreciate the law enforcement action taken at Kwong Fok Estate, Tai Po.  The police officers monitor the vehicles to see if the drivers have stopped their cars in front of the zebra-crossing, if there are passerby awaiting to cross the road.

I am a resident for Kwong Fok Estate and I always find that the vehicles do not let the passerby go first in the zebra-crossing, it is dangerous for the passerby and the drivers have violated related traffic law as well.

Please allow me to say thank you again for those management level who decided to take such law enforcement in the estate, and thank you those police officers for your hard work on enforcing the related law.

Regards,
Mr. Chan</content></item><item><title>2015-11-25 - Compliment of Police Officers of Western Division</title><content>I appreciate the prompt action of the police officers for helping me and my friend to trace his wallet lost inside a taxi from Admiralty to Kennedy Town.  The taxi driver was helpful and the wallet was returned to my friend within an hour.  I convey high regard for their enthusiasm.  Please keep the momentum and carry on the best protection of the HK citizen.  Thank you.

Cheers,
Miss Ma

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Sergeant 34877 WONG Man-dick, PC 17393 WONG King-sau, PC 17925 TSANG Tsz-chung and PC 34287 LEUNG Kwok-wai of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Western Division</content></item><item><title>2015-11-22 - Compliment of Police Officer of Yuen Long District</title><content>I am writing to thank you for a police officer who assisted me to investigate a pick-pocket case reported in Pat Heung Police Station in October 2015.

I sincerely thank you for his effort and professionalism to the case.

Miss Yeung 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 58199 CHENG Kam-cheung of District Investigation Team 2, Yuen Long District</content></item><item><title>2015-11-21 - Compliment of Police Officer of Central District</title><content>I found that I lost my wallet with my HKID card, credit cards and some cash in the taxi when I got off the taxi to Discovery Bay Pier due to my own absent mindedness. The taxi had already left the pier 2 minutes ago.  I saw a police vehicle with a Police Officer and reported the incident.  He was kind enough to drive me round the pier areas via the police vehicle to see if I could recognize the taxi driver for about 10 minutes.  Unfortunately with all the kind help from the police officer, I could not find the taxi driver even though I remembered the color of the shirt of the driver.  The officer was kind enough to explain the procedures to report the loss and tell me to report to the relevant banks for the ATM/credit cards loss. 

His attitude was sincere, helpful and professional.  I commended him for his professionalism and sincerity to help me in this crisis situation.  I salute to him and want to make this known to his superiors for his excellent and caring attitude at a time when I was miserable for the losses.

Ms. Kwan 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 48912 of District Traffic Team, Central District</content></item><item><title>2015-11-18 - Compliment on Police Officers of Wan Chai District</title><content>I am writing this letter, as I wanted to express my gratitude and appreciation to the members of Wan Chai District Investigation Team 3.

On a day of November 2015, some foreign currency was found missing in our apartment in Happy Valley.  The mentioned police team was requested to come to my apartment for further investigation of the case.  Initially, we were in no hope in resolving the case.  Especially no mark has been made on our money.

However, the investigation team has demonstrated highly professional examination and the full investigation has made the suspect admitted the crime on the spot.  Very good teamwork with clear role allocation of each member was observed which made us very impressive.  For instance, one with good analytical skill explained to us clearly the different scenarios and possible next steps; while some with good persuasive skill enabled the suspect to admit the crime after evidence was found, as well as reported the inspectors the details on how the crime happened.

The case was solved smoothly in a step by step approach.  The inspector has also kept us well informed of progress at all times even after the suspect was bring to the Police Station.  This incidence has surely enhanced the image and reputation of Hong Kong Police Force to us ! 

Thanks again for all that you have done. My family truly appreciate the services your team has provided.  I truly and entirely appreciate his help and may we offer a salute to all of you.

Connie

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Inspector YIP Pak-lun, Sergeant 754 NG Ting-hong, PC 209 LAW Chi-wing, PC 12740 HUI Ka-cheong, PC 12509 CHIU Sik-sun, PC 281 CHOW Wing-fat, PC 16113 CHOI Wai-yi and PC 7199 TUNG Wun-lan of District Investigation Team 3, Wan Chai District</content></item><item><title>2015-11-16 - Compliment on Police Officers of Wan Chai Division</title><content>Dear Sir,

At a midnight of November 2015, I waited for several minutes at the reception hall of Wan Chai Police Station but the wait was really worth it.  My case is not a complicated one but rather the opposite - a very simple.  And this is the third reported case made for the same 'missing person' - my husband who is suffering from dementia.  The first case was when he got lost whilst under the care of the Pamela Youde Hospital (he was lost in Chai Wan and was picked up in Central); the second was when he got lost by my maid (he was lost in Shau Kei Wan and was picked up in Wan Chai); and today was when he missed by his friends at a lunch gathering (he was lost in between Wan Chai and Causeway Bay and found IN Causeway Bay).  

He had gone to the washroom and soon lost his presence of mind and found himself wandering out of the restaurant to the streets.  The officers were very patient and thorough; they went to all the areas concerned; they talked to all the necessary parties familiar to him; and they talked to the caretakers of all the former places that he had stayed; and in the early evening (same day) they were able to locate him.  I didn't have the chance to thank the police in the past and didn’t witness how diligent they are in the cases.  Today I saw all that, they took me along in the police van till we finally picked him up and signed close the file.

I am very confident in the services, efficiency and capabilities of the Hong Kong police force (even in small matters) and I hope that in writing this, this would give them the needed initiative to keep up the good work.

Kindly extend my thanks, gratefulness and appreciation to these fine officers.

Yours sincerely,
Veronica 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Sergeant 50224 KWOK Hon-wing, Sergeant 53069 LEUNG Kwong-hung, Sergeant 57039 LEE Wing-yin, PC 18439 MA Kwok-ying, PC 22482 FUNG Wing-kwan, PC 17653 FU Yuen-ning and PC 10960 YEUNG Kam-lin of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Wan Chai Division</content></item><item><title>2015-11-12 - Compliment on Police Officers of Counter Terrorism and Internal Security Division</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I am writing to thank your colleagues, Station Sergeant LEE, Police Constable 1221 and Police Constable 11611 for your assistance.
 
My friend and I traveled from Melbourne, Australia, arriving at Hong Kong Airport on 1st October at approximately 10.30pm.  We were looking for a Taxi to take us to a hotel in Kowloon.

Unfortunately, we were the victims of a taxi scam and were robbed of $450 HK.  The thieves left us at an empty bus station late at night.  We were very frightened, we had no money or phone and we did not know how to find our hotel.

We will never forget how relieved we were when you assisted us and we are so very grateful for your help.  What began as a very bad experience for us ended well because of your friendly reassurance and willingness to help. Thank you.

Best Regards, 
Maree 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Station Sergeant LEE Wing-shum, PC 1221 LEUNG Wai-ho and PC 11611 HUNG Tung-man of Counter Terrorism Response Unit, Counter Terrorism and Internal Security Division</content></item><item><title>2015-11-06 - Compliment on Police Officer of Airport District</title><content>Dear Sir,

This is a compliment letter to show my appreciation to two police offers for their professionalism and dedication to help me to find my cell phone back.

I visited HK in September 2015 and lost my cell phone on the cab.  I called the police and those two officers showed up and helped me all the way to find the taxi driver and my cell phone.

I would like to show my warmest appreciation for their help and I feel very safe and being taken care of with such great police team around. Thank You !  

Best Regards,
Mr HAO

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 33988 LAU Hing-cheung and 52847 WONG Nam-tat of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Airport District</content></item><item><title>2015-11-05 - Compliment on Police Officers of Tseung Kwan O Division</title><content>Dear Sir,

There was a case of 2 persons got drunken at a midnight on 1st November 2015, lingering at Yau Yue Wan Village, Tseung Kwan O.

Sorry for causing trouble meanwhile. One of my family members got drunken and fell on the ground.  He just could not wake up and went home while I was also drunk as well. 

Thanks for the police officers attending this case. They were really helpful, going out of their way and sending him home.  This may not be their duty but they made such an effort to help, much appreciated! 

Regards,
Mr Chan</content></item><item><title>2015-11-03 - Compliment on Police Officer of Happy Valley Division</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 

I would like to send a letter to thank a police officer (Mr. Yuen) of Happy Valley Police Station.  He was on duty at report room in a morning of October 2015 when I reported the loss of my mobile phone. 

It was an intensely stressful experience for me as I have stored all seven years of my kids' photos since birth and they were not backed up.

Mr. Yuen was patient, calm and understanding in alleviating my concerns, efficient in explaining the situation and dutifully recorded my report with patience and efficiency.

Honestly, to me losing the mobile phone maybe a big thing personally but to the police, it's one of a million important things to handle but he nonetheless exhibited professionalism, courtesy and was very effective.  More often than not I see members of the public not appreciating the great effort of HK Police Force and it is so unfair.

Mr. Yuen managed to track, trace and find my phone within 2 hours. You can imagine my surprise and gratitude. He also took care to follow up to ensure that I did get it back from the taxi driver who called the Happy Valley Police Station and admitted he found the phone stuck in the creaks of the taxi door.

I believe it is only right that his superiors or police office in charge in Happy Valley Police Station know of his good action.  Mr. Yuen was very humble and claimed that he was only performing his duty, I do hope that this letter will serve as a reminder to the public that we are lucky to have such good Police Force and officers like Mr. Yuen in HK to help, support, serve and protect us.

It is only in the little things that we feel the Police Care !

Thank you again.

Regards,
Marina 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 54345 YUEN Ka-chun of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Happy Valley Division</content></item><item><title>2015-10-30 - Compliment on Police Officer of Airport District</title><content>I lost a luggage on taxi on the way to airport and reported to a police officer of Airport Police Station. Mr. CHENG of Airport Police Station was very responsive and went out of his way to help me. He has good working attitude and professionalism. Hong Kong has good legal and social system and Hong Kong Police has high integrity. We support you and hope you will continue to keep Hong Kong in good order.  Special thanks to Mr. CHENG and Hong Kong Police! 

Amanda

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 33799 CHENG Kwun-wa of Patrol Sub-unit 3, Airport District</content></item><item><title>2015-10-29 - Compliment on Police Officers of Central District</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I want to thank the police officers of Central Police Station who helped me out at the night of October 2015.  I forgot to take note of the car plate of the vehicle and the number of the police officers so I could not identify them.

I boarded a taxi at Bonham Road and the taxi driver refused to take me to Mongkok as he was unwilling to cross the harbour at that time. I told the taxi driver he should either take me the destination or to the nearest police station. Upon hearing so, he called for assistance and asked the police to come. The police officers arrived promptly and they had pleasant and helpful attitude. They handled the complaint in the most professional manner and took record of the complaint. They also explained the rules to the driver and that he indeed has no ground to refuse the journey.  

I am writing to thank the officers for handling the complaint in the most helpful, positive and professional manner. I should be grateful if you could kindly covey my thanks to them. Thank you.

Best Regards, 
Angie</content></item><item><title>2015-10-23 - Compliment on Police Officer of Pat Heung Division</title><content>I would like to show my appreciation to an Auxiliary Sergeant of Pat Heung Division. He is very responsive and polite.  He coordinated the traffic at the entrance of Milk Farm, Tai Mo Shan effectively and professionally in an afternoon of October 2015.  I have a very good impression on Hong Kong Police ! 

Kiko 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is Auxiliary Sergeant 6817 LAU Yip-hung of Patrol Sub-unit 3, Pat Heung Division</content></item><item><title>2015-10-20 - Compliment on Police Officers of Traffic Kowloon West Region</title><content>Dear Sir,

On 6 September 2015, my motorcycle had some problem while I was driving home in the No. 5 highway form Kowloon to Hong Kong.  As a result, my bike was unable to move in the highway as the back wheel was stuck.  Three Police officers were very helpful.  They provided some tools to me, and also helped me to remove that fabric.  However it was not successful because the back wheel was stuck, they helped me move the bike to the nearest exit.  I was very impressed by their politeness and helpfulness.  Many thanks!  

Best Regards, 
Tim

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Sergeant 52401 WONG Chi-keung, PC 34340 WONG King-fai and PC 11062 Man Ka-hing of Enforcement and Control Division, Kowloon West Region
</content></item><item><title>2015-10-15 - Compliment on Police Officer of Yau Tsim District</title><content>Dear Sir / Madam,

On a day of October 2015, I approached Tsim Sha Tsui Police Station for accompanying my wife to provide the information of a suspected deception and theft case.   

Throughout the process of information collection and statement taking, we did witness the professionalism of Madam CHAN in comprehension of complicated ideas by active listening to the victims with patience and sincere caring, and her high organization powers in presenting the accurate essential elements of information for follow up so as to uphold the justice in a highly professional manner.

We know the bitterness in handling public with ever-rising demand and unreasonable feedback to disciplined force in certain recent social scenarios, we see that there is a need to recognize the good deed and performance of frontline officers rather than only echoing discontent.

The senior management of her should be proud of having such a valuable asset under his command and we also thank her for her management in training the frontline to be of such high standard.

Please relay our deepest gratitude to Madam CHAN and her management, the team or her should be formally recognized to show the citizen's support and positive feedback to the police.

Best Reagrds, 
Mr. KWONG

Note : the officer praised in this letter is WPC 10921 CHAN Ho-hing of District Investigation Team 3 of Yau Tsim District</content></item><item><title>2015-10-14 - Compliment on Police Officer of Wan Chai Division and Happy Valley Division</title><content>Dear Sir,

I would like to show my appreciation to all the police officers involved in the incident with my friend in an evening on a day of August 2015, which subsequently involved both Happy Valley and Wan Chai Divisions. 

I would like to applause the officers for checking all floors of my friend's residential building, just to make sure he was on the roof top, and later taking me around in the police van to look for him.  I would like to express my gratitude for the teamwork from both divisions as they had acted professionally and sincerely put my friend's safety at first priority. 

Yours Sincerely,
Miss LAM 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Sergeant 54559 CHOI Sek-hun , Sergeant 33880 CHENG Kam-fai and PC 47537 LEUNG Chi-ming of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Wan Chai Division and PC 53089 SIT Man and PC 58904 TAM Kwai-yung of Patrol Sub-unit 1, Happy Valley Division</content></item><item><title>2015-10-05 - Compliment on Police Officers of Peak Sub-Division</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 

I would like to express my thanks for the top class service and support provided by each officer who assisted me on the evening of Tuesday 29th September 2015.  A young lady had become lost that evening whilst hiking on the peak and her phone battery had run out.  She could not find her way back to the Peak Tower and became distressed alone in the dark.  With the assistance of your officers she made it home and they took the time to ensure she was safe and well. 

All officers involved acted efficiently, professionally and with great care.  A true asset to your service.  Those directly involved were Police Officers of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Peak Sub-Division.

Other officers encountered that night were equally professional but I was unable to take all of their badge numbers.  Thank you to all involved.

Best Regards, 
Jonathan

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Sergeant 50977 WONG Wai-man, PC 33224 LAI Ting-pong, PC 50436 HAU Shing-hing and WPC 55653 YAU Yuk-chun of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Peak Sub-Division</content></item><item><title>2015-10-05 - Compliment on Police Officer of Western Division</title><content>Dear HK Police,

I would like to say thank you to the policeman, whom I did not manage to get his name recently. 

It was around noon time on 2015-09-26 when I drove to Hill Road for lunch.  There was a big lorry parking illegally ahead for offloading furniture.  I was unable to park my car behind as it blocked the path but they were so rude and refused to move forward to let my car in.  I was nervous and insulted by them.  When I was worried about what to do, a policeman came to ask me if there was any traffic accident.  I told the policeman about my concern and issue.  He was so helpful to get those people to move out and teach me how to park my car.  He was like a hero to me that time as I was relieved. 

I truly and entirely appreciate his help and may I offer a salute to all of you.

Yours sincerely,
Jenny</content></item><item><title>2015-09-27 - Compliment on Police Officer of Tsing Yi Division</title><content>Dear Sir,

     I am writing to express my appreciation to two police officers of Tsing Yi Police Station for their professional and mindful action in recovering my lost mobile phone at Tsing Yi area.  

     In an evening of September 2015, when I arrived home after having dinner in a shopping center of Tsing Yi, I discovered my mobile phone was left behind in the toilet of the shopping mall.  I immediately phoned the Security Office of mentioned shopping center requesting their assistance.  However, the slow action and negative attitude of the officer discouraged my hope of recovering the phone.  As the phone contained important personal information and some memorable photos, I needed to find it badly.  I had no alternative but to seek assistance from Tsing Yi Police Station.  With the concerted effort of two police officers, my mobile phone was found less than an hour after I reported to the duty officer of Tsing Yi Police Station. 
   
          I was really astonished by the efficiency of the officers.  Their positive attitude to ease the worry of citizens should be highly recognized.
                                                                      
Yours sincerely,
Lydia

Note : the officers praised in this letter are Sergeant 54110 CHAN Man-cheung and PC 15883 WONG Ka-ho of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Tsing Yi Division
</content></item><item><title>2015-09-15 - Compliment on Police Officer of Emergency Unit, Hong Kong Island</title><content>Dear HK Police,

I would like to say thank you to the policemen - 港島衝鋒隊, PC 6571, PC 11126 and WPC 321.  They are very helpful when I reported my apartment being locked inside this evening.  When I came home this evening and I found out that my home being locked inside and suspected being broken in by somebody.  I reported to my house management team and they helped me to report to the police.  The policemen came quickly for investigation.  It seemed that the door lock was locked accidentally. They are very polite, and tried to make sure my apartment is ok.  Finally the door was opened by the goldsmith and my home is safe and fine.  I would like to appreciate the quick response of the HK Police and their professionalism in dealing with such a simple case.  Salute to all of you.
Thanks.

Yours sincerely,
Wong

Note : the officer praised in this letter are WPC 321 CHAN Nga-tung, PC 6571 CHIU Kin-wah and PC 11126 LEUNG Ka-shing of Platoon 2, Emergency Unit Hong Kong Island.
</content></item><item><title>2015-09-10 - Compliment on Police Officer of Kowloon City District</title><content>I really appreciate the police officers near my child's kindergarten situated at Cumberland Road every morning in the past few days.  There have been fewer vehicles parked on the pavement which caused obstruction to pedestrian.  I find the area safer for my child when we walk to school.  I am also thankful for the fines given to the people who keep their cars idling while waiting.  This action makes the area less polluted.  Thank you. 

Ms Mamta 
</content></item><item><title>2015-09-06 - Compliment on Police Officers of Central District</title><content>I lost my mobile phone at the end of August 2015.  Therefore, I reported to Central Police Station.  Later the lost property was found by a kind taxi driver and returned to me.  I would like to thank all police personnel involved for the report.  Thank You ! 

Monica Cheung
</content></item><item><title>2015-09-03 - Compliment on Police Officers of Tsuen Wan District</title><content>Dear Sir, 

In a morning of August 2015, I walked along a water trail near Ting Kau, Tsuen Wan and found a porcupine that had fallen into the water work channel and could not get out from it.

Then I phoned the police.  Afterwards, police officers of Tsuen Wan Police Station came with Fire Service Department within short time.  After considerable effort, they saved the animal and sent it to SPCA. 

I'd like to thank the officers of Tseun Wan Police Station for their professional and courteous assistance.  I feel sorry that I did not note the officers’ names but please pass my appreciation to your staff.  Thank You! 

Kind Regards,
Mr. Horvath</content></item><item><title>2015-08-28 - Compliment on Police Officer of Traffic Kowloon East Region</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 

Recently I was pulled over and booked by a policeman for speeding at Clear Water Bay Road, Kowloon.  This was my first traffic infringement in the past 11 years since I have lived here.  Although I annoyed with myself for speeding, I am writing to say the policeman who booked me was the nicest encounter I have had ever with any policeman.  He was so polite but fair and friendly, restoring my faith that there is nice policeman out in the community.  Thank you!

Best Regards, 
Helen

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 34578 LAI Sin-hing of Enforcement and Control Division, Kowloon East Region</content></item><item><title>2015-08-26 - Compliment on Police Officer of North Point Division</title><content>In a Sunday’s morning of August 2015, the jogging lane of Victoria Park was full of people.  I witnessed a Madam (Madam Cheng) and her team (including 2 male police officers) making great effort in maintaining good order and safety of the lane. They had shown high proficiency in crowd control and patience in communicating with people of different ethnics.  Please do let them know they are being appreciated. The Police Force should be proud of their performance.  Thank You ! 

Mr Tsoi 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is Auxiliary Station Sergeant CHENG Suk-yin of Patrol Sub-unit 3, North Point Division.</content></item><item><title>2015-08-24 - Compliment on Police Officer of Kwai Chung Division</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam,

I am writing to express my deep appreciation for the helpful attitude of the policeman who had provided good support and assistance to me and my family members when we were facing sudden death of our mother in late July.

Having noticed my mother sudden coma and death, we were so worried and distressed at that time.  Fortunately, we had been given a lot help from the responsible policeman in the hospital and at the mortuary.  Hence, we were strongly impressed by the helpful attitude of him and we would like to say thank you to him for his kindness and good support to us.

Best Regards, 
Alain 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 58329 WONG Io-cheong of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Kwai Chung Division. </content></item><item><title>2015-08-24 - Compliment on Police Officer of Happy Valley Division</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 

I am writing to express my sincerest thanks to two of your young officers serving in the Happy Valley Police Station.  They went extraordinary lengths to contact me when a good citizen handed in my wallet after it slipped out from my pocket.  What they would not have known is that I am due to fly overseas on holidays in the coming days which would have clearly been jeopardised with my HKID, bank cards etc.

The officers were outgoing, extremely helpful and they represented your organisation perfectly.  It is all too easy as a member of the public to view workers from government departments with a certain degree of ambivalence.   But when the staff showed such personality while committing to the responsibilities of the job it is memorable and I will hold the HK police in the highest regard as a result.  My Sincerest thanks guys, you are doing an excellent job !

Yours sincerely,
Jamie 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 18265 HO Ka-wai and PC 9945 LAW Chi-wai of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Happy Valley Division</content></item><item><title>2015-08-17 - Compliment on Police Officer of Tseung Kwan O Division</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam,

In a morning of August 2015, I called the police in Tseung Kwan O Division and asked for help to connect with my sister.  I live in USA and my sister (70 years old) lives in Tseung Kwan O by herself.  I could not reach my sister for three weeks by calling her cell phone (she does not have a home phone).  Every time when I called, it was said that the number was not registered.  I did not know what happened to her and felt so worried about my sister’s safety.  I made a lot of phone calls to different organizations in Hong Kong, but nobody could help me.  Then I had no choice but to call the police.  A female officer collected information over the phone, and coordinated between me and a male officer who found my sister.  Finally I talked to my sister through the police officer’s cell phone.  Without the help of the police officers, my sister would not notice that the phone company canceled her cell phone service.  

My sister and I really appreciate the police officers' great help.  I was so moved by these two police officers and their skills to handle international cases in such a professional and efficient way.

Thank you from the bottom of my heart.

Best Regards, 
Ms LI
</content></item><item><title>2015-08-07 - Compliment on Police Officer of Wong Tai Sin District</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 
								     
My elder sister was a victim in a deception case.  After we reported the case to the police, two officers soon arrived at our home for assistance.  I witnessed the high quality and high level of professionalism of the two officers, showing care, patience, and sympathy.  They care about citizen's benefit first as they were willing to wait until my sister went to the bank to freeze her bank account and then gave us a ride to file a report at the station.  Both my sister and myself felt touched, and after living in a few countries including HK, China and USA, I feel the urge to file this compliment to extend our gratitude to the two officers, who have exemplified a model of highest standard of work ethic and professionalism that is second to none of any of the police forces of the places I have lived before.  I am proud to tell everyone that I am a HK citizen because HK has a police force like this. 

Best Regards, 
Mr Fong

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 49003 LIU Hon-hung and PC 17004 TANG Hoi-san of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Wong Tai Sin District
</content></item><item><title>2015-07-25 - Compliment on Police Officer of Shatin Division</title><content>At a midnight of July 2015, I called the police to ask for help as the soccer pitch at Sha Tin Area had all the lights on and it affected some buildings nearby.  As a result, we couldn't fall asleep.

We called 999 and were then told that police officers would go for a check.  To our delight, 30 minutes later, the lights were turned off. 

We would like to send our appreciation to the officers that helped us in this matter efficiently.

Thank you.

Gloria</content></item><item><title>2015-07-23 - Compliment on Police Officer of Ma On Shan Division</title><content>I would like to praise the service provided by the Task Force Unit of Ma On Shan Police Station.

In a midnight of July 2015, an unknown male assaulted my daughter and I reported the case to Ma On Shan Police Station later.  After a few days, the Task Force Unit of Ma On Shan Police Station arrested a male who was a suspect.

I wanted to let everyone know that those police officers provided an outstanding service and were very patient and helpful.  We need to appreciate and give credit to the local police officers that they deserve.

Ms SHEK 
</content></item><item><title>2015-07-08 - Compliment on Police Officer of Traffic New Territories South Region</title><content>I would like to praise a police officer (PC 34879) Mr Au Yueng Hak Man, who belongs to an Accident Investigation Team of Traffic New Territories South Region.  I thank him for his excellent services, polite manner and extreme patience when handling my complaints about a illegal traffic incident somewhere in Tsuen Wan Area.  Many Thanks!

Andrew

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 34879 of Investigation and Support, Accident Investigation Team, New Territories South Region</content></item><item><title>2015-07-08 - Compliment on Police Officer of Airport District </title><content>On a day of June 2015, we took a taxi from Harbour Grand Hotel in Hong Kong to Hong Kong International Airport.  After we checked in, we realized that we had left one of our haversacks in the taxi.

We went to lodge a police report with regards to our lost property.  CHEUNG Sir is the police officer who handled our case.  Due to the limited time we had before boarding, his swift response was really helpful for us.  He managed to track the car owner of the aforesaid taxi, and the owner later gave him the driver's number and managed to call the driver.  CHEUNG Sir even went the extra mile to accompany us to the departure door to help us locate the driver. 

If not him, we would have lost or would not be able to retrieve our laptop and other stuff in the haversack on time.  We really appreciate his helpfulness and when we were desperate, he made it so much easier for us.  We would like to express our gratitude towards him. 

Miss NG

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 33222 CHEUNG Yau-hong of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Airport District </content></item><item><title>2015-06-30 - Compliment on Police Officer of North Point Division </title><content>To whom it may concern, 

I would like to send my sincere appreciation to two police officers of North Point Police Station for their patience and professional attitude when resolving my dispute incident recently.

Thanks and best regards, 
Jimmy

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 16186 CHAN Chi-kit and PC 17681 TAI Tsz-ho of Patrol Sub-unit 4, North Point Division
</content></item><item><title>2015-06-28 - Compliment on Police Officer of Wan Chai District </title><content>Dear Sir, 

On a day of June 2015, my flatmate and I were home when the officers of District Special Duty Squad, Team 2 of Wan Chai Police Station came to collect evidence and arrest the women next door who had been running a brothel in the apartment directly next door to us.  The whole situation was handled very professionally and the officers we spoke to were very polite and kind in taking time to explain what was happening next door.  The entire operation ran very smoothly considering the media attention outside our building.  We really appreciate the actions being taken and the manner in which it was carried out as it has been very difficult to live next door to such an establishment. 

Resident of Wan Chai </content></item><item><title>2015-06-27 - Compliment on Police Officer of Hung Hom Division </title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 				     

In a afternoon of May 2015, my stuff were stolen from my car in car park and a police officer of Hung Hom Police Station helped me to watch the CCTV in Whampoa Garden control room.  I thank him for his time and effort.  He is professional and very nice.  I sincerely appreciate his effort and respect the police officer.  Many Thanks!

Best Regards, 
Mr Mak 	

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 14125 WONG Hon-chiu of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Hung Hom Division</content></item><item><title>2015-06-24 - Compliment on Police Officer of Traffic New Territories North Region</title><content>Dear Sir / Madam,

I am writing to commend your officer from NTN Traffic Team, Mr. Cheung for his courteous and professional approach to handle my case.
 
We filed a report to Yuen Long Police Station over a “hit and run” involving our village property on a day of June, 2015 and your officer Mr. Cheung responded and arrived at our village shortly the same day.

Mr. Cheung, as one of the officers arrived at the scene, communicated with us in a very professional and polite manner while we were checking the CCTV footages together.  He patiently and clearly explained the procedures to us step by step.  More importantly, he showed his attention by listening carefully to our enquiries, and answered well.  That made the whole investigation extremely smooth and efficient, and I must say our villagers are very much impressed.  

With the great assistance provided by the police, we managed to contact the driver who is responsible for the damage property, and settled the case without much hassle.

However, such good work by Mr. Cheung should not be gone unnoticed, and I would like to take this opportunity to express my gratitude to the Police Force on this case, and also I would like to give my compliment to Mr. Cheung and his unit commander who must have good leadership to have such exemplary officer.  

A job very well done, thank you !

Yours Faithfully,

William

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 9060 CHEUNG Lu-yi of Traffic Accident Investigation Team 1, New Territories North Region

</content></item><item><title>2015-06-18 - Compliment on Police Officers of Wong Tai Sin District</title><content>Dear Sir / Madam,

First of all I would like to show my appreciation on the quick response of your officers in dealing with a traffic obstruction case at Ngau Chi Wan area in a morning of June 2015.  I have sent an e-report via web and got a call from one of your officers within some time.  Yet I don't know whether the concerned car had left the scene or not but I really appreciated your officers' quick response. 

Meanwhile, I admired the effort the Police Force had made so as to maintain HK as a safe place to live.  You all really deserve a big clap from us.

Yours faithfully,
Ms Tang
</content></item><item><title>2015-06-12 - Compliment on Police Officers of Tai Po District</title><content>Dear Sirs / Madams,

I would like to express my gratitude to Sheung Shui Division uniformed police officers and all CID officers of Team 8 Tai Po District for their professionalism, courteousness, patience and efficiency during a recent investigation of my theft of bicycle case. 

Those uniformed police officers from Sheung Shui Division arrived promptly and took time to listen carefully, investigated and noted the details of the case.  They explained to me what I have to do and answered all my queries.  They are very helpful, patient and supportive.  Then, those Team 8 CID officers from Tai Po District did the same job according to the procedure.

A few days later, I found my bicycle at Chi Yin Lane, Sheung Shui.  Those uniformed police officers and CID officers arrived immediately and helped to keep a watchful eye on the bicycle, hopefully to arrest the thief.  They showed their great responsibility and accountability by staying then and there in order to keep my stolen bicycle under in a safe status.

The excellent service provided by those police officers also reflects the professional leadership leading to the high quality service of the HK Police Force.  Please help me to pass my sincere thanks to all of the police officers involved in my case.  Their performance is superb, thank you ! 

Best Regards, 
Mr Chong 
</content></item><item><title>2015-06-02 - Compliment on Police Officer of Traffic New Territories North Region</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I write to express my sincere thanks to a traffic police officer who has rendered his help to me this morning.
 
I was on my way to work and was stuck in a traffic jam outside the Fanling public swimming pool on San Wan Road of Sheung Shui, at about 7am today. 
 
About 10 minutes later, a young male police officer approached me and told me that a taxi had an accident in the road ahead and it would take quite a while to move it out, clear the mess and resume normal traffic flow.  He asked if I could turn my car up to a road divider so that I could make a u turn and head off.  I said I could try but I am not very good in reversing the car, so I asked if he could help me to do so, and to my delight, he agreed and hopped in and did a beautiful job, as he got out of the car, he also reminded me to set the car seat position (as he had to move the car seat back to fit in) before I drive off. 
 
I cannot express enough of my heartfelt gratitude to this officer who had been most helpful and friendly, and gone out of his way to help me.  He could have ignored me and let me sit there in the car for hours.  Please pass on my appreciation to him.  Keep up with the good work ! 
 
Best regards, 
Miss Luk 
 
Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 8739 YEUNG Chak-ming of Enforcement and Control Division, New Territories North Traffic Patrol Sub-unit 1
</content></item><item><title>2015-05-30 - Compliment on Police Officer of Central District</title><content>Dear Sir/ Madam,

I am writing to express my sincere appreciation and heartfelt gratitude to a police officer of Central Police Station. On a day of May 2015, at Central Harbourfront Event Space, my sister and I were involved in an Internet crime.  We had brought Cavalia tickets online.  We were deceived with the price difference at $800 with no possible solution or compensation from Cavalia.  We could not go to the show since the tickets were not at the correct price and did not belong to us. 

We reported the case to the police through 999.  A police officer of Central District came with a helpful and friendly manner.  He easily understood the situation with active listening skills and swiftly handled the matter.  He patiently explained the reasons why Cavalia would not offer the compensation or difficulties in solving the case.  Despite the above, he tended to deal the case with empathy and innate kindness.  He tried to contact different sources for help.  At last, with the constant and effective negotiation, he relayed our situation to the box office manager and solved the problem for us.  Cavalia kindly offered us tickets on the following date.  We did not expect that we would be treated with such a great help from the policeman. We were extremely thankful to him. 

In the whole process, your staff showed high degree of professionalism, kindness and effectiveness.  He is a young policeman with good heart, sound manner and mediation skills.  I hope that through this letter, his work will be highly recognized and respected since his great effort in maintaining or uplifting the honors of the Police Force.  It is hoped that his attitudes, conducts and skills will make him one of the most honorable policemen in the Force. 

Yours faithfully,
Miss Wong

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 17043 SHI Yu-shing of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Central District 
</content></item><item><title>2015-05-28 - Compliment on Police Officers of Hung Hom Division </title><content>Dear Sir, 

This is a letter of praise for the police officers who responded to an incident in Hung Hom area which occurred on a day in May 2015, involving the loss of my designer label change bag that I dropped at a the curb where my car was parked while offloading some groceries.

Upon arriving at the scene, police officers of Hung Hom Police Station immediately took down the details of the missing change bag and persuaded the security guards to review CCTV footage taken of the surrounding area where the change bag was allegedly lost.

Upon review of the CCTV footage, it was quickly identified that the perpetrator was in fact a tenant staying in the building.  With assistance from the police officers, the perpetrator, a Mongolian male, was immediately accosted while he came out for walk. The police officers then requested to attend his flat and show them the change bag found outside the building containing all of my personal data and most importantly, a highly confidential memory stick.

Although the perpetrator was not arrested at the time, it is unlikely I would have recovered the lost change bag without the efforts of the abovementioned police officers.  They are a credit to the Hong Kong Police Force, literally a needle found in a haystack.  I am happy to provide a statement as needed if the matter is taken any further, and would like to thank these police officers for taking my request at face value, and achieving an equally efficient and unbelievably positive result!

Yours sincerely,
Keith 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are SGTA 3585 CHAN Kam-fai, PC 2948 MOK Hei-lun and PC 16502 HO Yim-ching of Patrol Sub-unit 1, Hung Hom Division 
</content></item><item><title>2015-05-26 - Compliment on Police Officer of Traffic Investigation Group, New Territories North Region</title><content>Dear Sir,
 
I really think that your officer Madam CHAN has a very good understanding of my case of complaint.  She has also demonstrated a very swift and accurate account of the description resulting in a written statement without any mistake.  Her Chinese writing capability is very good that the other police officers should share and learn from her.

On the other hand, she has grasped the time gap e.g. on the April 17, 2015 that I was only available and convenient to give statement when she contacted me around noon that day.  She has shown respect to complainants' special circumstances of time constraint and has showed diligence when I requested her to take the statement on April 17, 2015 (on the same date).  She has impressed me because she has tried to accomplish my request to give statement on the same day despite short notice.  She is a very efficient officer in the HK Police Force.

Thank her effort, and her efficiency and effectiveness at work.  She is definitely an asset of the HK Police Force.

Best Regards,
Lyndon

Note : the officer praised in this letter is WPC 5550 CHAN Ching-sze of Team 1, Traffic Investigation Group, New Territories North Region
</content></item><item><title>2015-05-22 - Compliment on Police Officers of Aberdeen Division </title><content>Dear Sir/ Madam,
 
I would like to express my appreciation for the excellent service provided by the three police officers of Aberdeen Police Station.  I highly appreciated the kind assistance given by the police officers, who demonstrated very strong “customer-focus” professionalism, and made it my most pleasant servicing experience with Police team so far.

The excellent service provided by the three police officers also reflects your professional leadership leading to the high quality service of your team.  Thank You.

Regards,
Ricky

Note : the officers praised in this letter are SGT 33925 WONG Yun-wan, PC 5379 LO Hin-tang and PC 16998 LEUNG Wing-hang of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Aberdeen Division
</content></item><item><title>2015-05-15 - Compliment on Police Officers of Yaumatei Division</title><content>I was on business travel to Dalian in China and decided to take a few days on my return journey to explore HK as I had heard a lot about it.  After a long day walking and sightseeing in HK, I took a meal in a local restaurant in Kowloon area.

In short, I got into a difficult situation when I had problems paying for a bill with a Visa card.  Officer PC 11331, supported by his fellow officer PC 18673, handled the problem in an EXCEPTIONAL WAY: tactful, balanced, supportive; and helped me through this situation with the restaurant staff.

For many years, I have heard that the HK Police Force is an outstanding organization - I can now say I have experienced this first hand.  Both officers are credits to your Force.  Congratulations.

Mr Danny Berry

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 11331 CHAN Yat-ho and PC LIU King-leung attached to Patrol Sub-unit 2, Yaumatei Division.
</content></item><item><title>2015-05-09 - Compliment on Police Officers of Central District</title><content>My client has transferred funds via Internet banking to an incorrect bank account.  The bank advised us to report the case to the police.

I reported the case at the Police Service Centre in Central asking for information of the procedure and the documents required.  Two policemen there were basically unable to handle my inquiry until WPC 8334 took over my case.  The female officer was very helpful.  She understood my question，concern and could explain to me what we had to do.  She was firm and clear, and also pleasant and nice.

To be honest，I merely needed to know what we should do if we needed to take further action.  The madam explained the case very clearly and thoroughly.  Although I am extremely busy, I feel like sending in this compliment to the officers who helped me.  The madam is capable.  Thanks a lot.

Note : the officers praised in this letter are WPC 8334 HUI Ying and two officers working at Police Service Centre, Central District
</content></item><item><title>2015-05-12 - Compliment on Police Officers of Sha Tin Division</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam,

I had a dispute with a mainland female on a bus stopping at Sha Tin Town Centre Terminus at a night in May 2015.  Her husband made a 999 call, claiming that his wife had been attacked.

I wish to express my heartfelt thanks to the station sergeant, the two sergeants and the two police constables who came for investigation that night.  They had made relentless efforts in helping me settle the dispute and shown the greatest perseverance during the investigation.  I am thankful to the station sergeant in particular.  He was decisive and experienced.  Under his excellent leadership, his team had demonstrated professionalism to the highest level.

Please pass my note of gratitude to the police officers of Sha Tin Police Station.    Hong Kong Police is the best ! 

Regards,

Citizen
</content></item><item><title>2015-05-09 - Compliment on Police Officers of Mong Kok District</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 

A few months ago, I bought a smart phone at a commercial center in Mong Kok. However, the phone ID code was not the same as the code on the invoice but the seller had sold it to me as new.  It definitely did not work after some months, showing hardware problems.  Then I went to the shop on 2015-04-23 and the seller called the Police because he thought he was right.

Thank you for the quick arrival of the police officers of Mong Kok Police Station. Afterwards, they handled the case in excellent English professionally.  Many Thanks.

Yours faithfully, 

Puschnerat

Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 45858 YUEN Wing-shing and PC 18332 YIP Kwan-ki of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Mong Kok District 
</content></item><item><title>2015-04-28 - Compliment on Police Officer of Wan Chai Division</title><content>Dear Sir,

My compliment is regarding a case handled by a female police officer (Madam POON) of Wan Chai Police Station.  She and her collogue have been very helpful during this case.  They arrived promptly and took the time to listen to and note the details of the case.  Madam POON speaks very good English which is essential in this case as I am from Belgium and unable to speak Chinese.

Their patience and accuracy resulted in successfully resolving the case.  Please help to pass my thanks to them and their supervisor.

Best Regards, 
Mr. Beig	

Note : one of the officer praised in this letter is WPC 12348 POON Ka-ying of Patrol Sub-unit 3, Wan Chai Division
</content></item><item><title>2015-04-07 - Compliment on Police Officer of Tsuen Wan District  </title><content>Dear Sir,                                                  

I would like to give my compliment to a police office for his whole-hearted assistance on the day when my mother and I went to Tsuen Wan Chinese Permanent Cemetery.

On 6 April, I drove to the cemetery and meant to park at Sunley Centre but then I was stopped by the police where I think is Wing Tak Street due to road closure.  I was then advised to drive away and park somewhere else. 

Yet, taking my old mother in my car, I was in a quandary if I should drop my mother off so that she did not have to walk all the way back to the cemetery from a car park which I was not sure how far it was. 

Seeing my hesitation, the young policeman showed his understanding and tried his best to address my problem instead of just driving me away.

Patiently explaining to me on the one hand as to how to drive back to the car parks nearby, the young policeman carefully assisted my mother to get off and leave the road ensuring the safety of this old lady while easing my tension at the same time.

For a policeman who had been standing under the sun for some time to maintain the order and who might have come across difficult visitors, this policeman remained polite and sincere demonstrating his respect and passion for his own profession

I trust that this policeman is not an exception and I am confident that our policemen in general can truly live up to the name of the Hong Kong Police Force to protect Hong Kong people in every possible way. 

Thank You! 

Bonnie Tang

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PCA 2817 CHAN Chi-fai of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Tsuen Wan District 

</content></item><item><title>2015-03-31 - Compliment on Police Officers of Cheung Sha Wan Division </title><content>Dear Sir, 

I am writing to you on behalf of my mother, who went to Cheung Sha Wan Police Station to collect her lost purse.  The officers there were very helpful and my mother received excellent services.  She would like to express her gratitude to all those in the Police Station who had rendered her help.

Once again, thank you very much for your kind assistance!

Sincerely
Cordianne 
</content></item><item><title>2015-03-28 - Compliment on Police Officers of Western Division </title><content>Dear Sirs,

We would like to show our appreciation and gratitude to all those police officers who were on patrol at the entrance of Pok Fu Lam Road Cemetery, Pok Fu Lam Road at around 10:00 on 2015-03-28.  Their sincerity, professionalism and medical knowledge were demonstrated in helping out my father, who fell down at the bus stop just outside the Cemetery at Pok Fu Lam Road Road. 

My father was very grateful for their help and care when those police officers were offering all those helpful assistance. Thank You！

Warm regards,

Mr Wong’s family
</content></item><item><title>2015-03-21 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear Madams/Sirs,

I was visiting Hong Kong for a few days during CNY and had the opportunity to interact with a handful of police officers.  On the first occasion I filed a police report against a taxi driver who overcharged me on a ride from the airport to my hotel.  On the second occasion we were down near the waterfront in Kowloon during the fireworks celebration and asked police advice, directions, etc. 

I must say each of the officers we interacted with were the highest quality police officers I have ever met globally.  They were professional, courteous, helpful, in great physical condition and very concerned about our well-being.  It was an absolute pleasure to interact with them.  I travel the world and I have never met such high quality police officers.  All credit to your department and system for having some of the best law enforcement representatives I have ever seen globally.  What an absolute delight and so refreshing.  An unexpected highlight of our trip.  

Keep up the great work.  Your officers are model for how police should be globally.

Kind regards
Joshua 
</content></item><item><title>2015-03-15 - Compliment on Police Officers of Tsuen Wan District</title><content>Dear Sir, 
					     
In an evening of March 2015, a theft case occurred in our school.  Upon our report, police officers of Tsuen Wan Police Station turned up to our school.  They stayed in the school office for more than 2 hours to watch the Closed Circuit Television (CCTV) to see if there was any suspect involved.  After they found out the suspect as one of our school caretakers, they immediately called officers of crime unit for help.  When we were waiting, the police officers helped me to solve some problems and reminded me to take care of my personal belongings.  Finally, the suspect was caught.  Please accept my appreciation to their serious and sincere attitude.  Many Thanks. 

Best Regards,  
Mr. Hung 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are SGT 34570 FONG Chi-ming, WPC 14735 WONG Yuen-shan and PC 17107 FAN Kam-ho of Patrol Sub-unit 2 Tsuen Wan District and PC 758 LAU Chi-chung of District Investigation Team 1, Tsuen Wan District.    
</content></item><item><title>2015-03-10 - Compliment on Police Officers of Wan Chai Division </title><content>Dear Sir/Madam,

I am writing to express my appreciation for the assistance rendered to me by five police officers of Wan Chai Police Station. 

On a day in February 2015, I left my belongings in a female toilet at a shopping centre in Wan Chai Area.	When I returned to the female toilet after a few minutes intending to retrieve my belongings, they were missing already and I suspected that they had been taken by someone.	 I then called the police for assistance.

Shortly afterwards, two police officers of Wan Chai Police Station arrived at the scene and started investigation immediately.  3 police officers from crime unit later arrived at the scene too.  Throughout the investigation process, all of them showed a high degree of professionalism and efficiency in discharging their duties.  They remained helpful, patient, and polite even under pressure.	In particular, I would like to thank a female uniform officer for carefully examining related premises of the shopping centre to try to locate my belongings instead of just treating the case as a trivial one.	 I am also deeply impressed by the fact that the male uniform officer took his initiative to try to locate the suspects in the surrounding areas and within a very short period of time, he was able to apprehend the two ladies who had apparently taken my belongings.

To sum up, I found both the uniform officers and crime unit officers involved in my case to be very well-trained, well-supervised, and dedicated.  I would like to extend my heartfelt gratitude to all of them.  I am sure the high performance standard of the mentioned officers is important in maintaining the overall high quality of the Hong Kong Police Force.

Yours faithfully,
Miss WONG 

Note : two of the officers praised in this letter are PC 7991 LAM Yi-ho and WPC 18342 CHAN Sim-ling of Patrol Sub-unit 2, Wan Chai Division 
</content></item><item><title>2015-03-08 - Compliment on Police Officers of Tseung Kwan O Division </title><content>Dear Sir, 

Recently, we have had 3 incidents of burglary which occurred within 2 weeks.  We are very afraid about both our safety and the complex of which we live in.  Your officers have been very helpful in regard to easing our worries.  I have confidence in the Hong Kong Police Force.  I wish that police officers could have more power in hands.  You also have the full support of our families.  We are always behind the Hong Kong Police Force in spirit.      

Regards, 
Marcus 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are SSGT CHAN Hoi-chiu, PC 4448 YIP Chi-sing and PC 9217 MAN Kin-ho of Task Force Sub-unit, Tseung Kwan O Division
</content></item><item><title>2015-03-06 - Compliment on Police Officers of Tai Po Division</title><content>I filled an online Telephone Nuisance report to the HK Police in Aug 2014 concerning a HK male resident that used to work for us in Canada.  This male was making serious sexual harassment phone calls to female employees with an unknown number in HK.  This male boarded a direct flight from HK to Toronto in 2014 and showed up at our offices.  He was later arrested and deported by Canadian authorities, but he continued the nuisance calls after his deportation which prompted me to contact the HK Police.  I had little to offer in regards to information on how to locate this male in HK.  Chief Inspector William HO of Tai Po Police Station kept me informed which made the female staff in the office more relaxed knowing that someone was taking care of the situation in HK where the suspect was living.  I'm pretty sure the Chief Inspector’s workload was substantial and this incident would be down on his to do list.  I appreciate his enthusiasm / customer service in not only serving the citizens of HK but also the citizens of another country.  As a result of Chief Inspector HO's actions, you now have almost 400 staff members at our head office in Canada with a positive view of the HK Police Force.  Chief Inspector HO should be commended for going that extra mile in helping us.  As for Inspector Sophia CHEUNG, I appreciate the follow-up emails finalizing the issue for now, but leaving the door open in case the issue reappears down the road.  On behalf of our company and myself, I would appreciate it if you would pass on our thanks from Canada to them.

Best Regards, 
Robert

Note : the officers praised in this letter are retired Chief Inspector HO Siu-ting, William and Woman Inspector CHEUNG Kwan-ting, Sophia of Tai Po District
</content></item><item><title>2015-03-02 - Compliment on Police Officers of Yuen Long District </title><content>Commissioner of the Police, 

In the past few months, a Chinese male involved in many incidents had been causing a lot of disturbance in our estate.  We received repeated complaints about his harassment and tricks on other residents in the estate.  As a result, our security guards had to be specially deployed to keep a close eye on his movement once he appeared in order to guard against possible mishaps.  So, both our tenants and the Management Office suffered a lot from the deviant behaviour of this man. 

On one day of January 2015, Inspector WONG led his investigation team of Yuen Long District to handle a case of malicious damage which occurred in Tin Yat Estate.  On that day, the aforesaid male was found deliberately breaking the break-glass from floor to floor in the estate.  About ten break-glasses were found.  The culprit was subsequently arrested by a member of investigation team. 

I am writing to express my deepest appreciation and thankfulness to your Senior Inspector WONG and his investigation team of Yuen Long District 

Best regards,
Staff of Management Office 
 								     
Note : one of the officer praised in this letter is Senior Inspector WONG Sze-pan of District Investigation Team 5, Yuen Long District  
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-26 - Compliment on Police Officer of Traffic Investigation Group, New Territories South Region</title><content>Dear Sir, 

      My appreciation to Miss SHUM of Team 2, Traffic Investigation Group, New Territories South Region.  I am pleased with the courteous manner and helpful attitude of the female officer.  The efficient services are able to meet citizens’ need.  Thank You !

Best Regards, 
Mrs. IP   

Note : the officer praised in this letter is WPC 57058 SHUM Wing-chi of Team 2, Traffic Investigation Group, New Territories South Region
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-23 - Compliment on Police Officers of Railway District</title><content>Dear Sir,

I am an Indian who visited HK in February.  On 2015-02-11, while I was returning from Hong Kong to India, I left a laptop in the dickey of a taxi.  When I realized that I had left my laptop in the taxi, it was already late as the taxi had left the place.  I immediately approached a police officer of Hong Kong MTR station and informed him of the incident.  The police officer was so kind and helpful to me.  He took me to police post, made me comfortable there and listened to my complaint patiently.  He noted my complaint and handed over some official papers of complaint to me.  He assured me with all possible help and traced the taxi and helped me in getting my lost property back.  I am grateful to Hong Kong Police for the help.  Please accept my appreciation for Hong Kong Police.  Thank You !

Best Regards, 
Mr. Kuldeep 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 7371 CHAN Tsun-yin of Lantau Airport Line, Railway District
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-22 - Compliment on Police Officer of Traffic Hong Kong Island Region </title><content>In a morning of February, I saw a police officer handle a traffic incident involving a public mini-bus and a truck lorry in the busy road junction of Lockhart Road and Marsh Road with firm attitude and effective manner.  As a result, they made the traffic flow in that junction smoothly and finished the traffic incident in a short period of time.  Appreciation should be given to this police officer.

Mr.Au 

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 49759 LEUNG Wai-man of Patrol Sub-unit 1, Enforcement and Control Team, Traffic Hong Kong Island Region

</content></item><item><title>2015-02-20 - Compliment on Police Officers of Airport District </title><content>Dear all, 

In a morning of February, my wife and I took a taxi from the airport taxi station back to our home.  Because we live nearby, the red taxi driver refused to take us home shortly after departing from the taxi stand and eventually became very aggressive (yelling/cursing) and ultimately stopped the car at a cross section refusing to drive further.  

We were very fortunate that two police officers arrived at the scene shortly after we called the police.  Both of them were very professional in handling the situation. Despite the taxi driver's condescending attitude, the police officers remained courteous and they professionally and effectively handled the case.  We were able to find another taxi to go home shortly afterwards.

Both my wife and I are very grateful for their assistance that night and want to write to extend our gratitude.  Thank you very much!

Best regards,
Vic
								     
Note : the officers praised in this letter are PC 52847 WONG Nam-tat and PC 34286 YAM Chor-tak of Patrol Sub-unit 2 , Airport District 
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-19 - Compliment on Police Officers of Happy Valley Division</title><content>On a day in January 2015, police officers of Happy Valley Division were called to our home as I raised a dispute with my domestic helper.  The domestic helper refused to leave our home though her employment was terminated.  She called the police to assist her.

The police officers arrived very quickly and spoke with both sides to understand the situation.  Afterwards, they spoke with my helper.  Finally, she agreed to leave.

The police officers were professional in their handling of this matter.  They were also friendly and patient and went out of their way to help.  I would like to thank all of them very much for their assistance on a very stressful day. 

Ms. Lam 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are SGT 48854 LING Hong, PC 11786 WONG Wai-kit, PCA 6475 TAM Wai-cheung and WPC 16791 TSOI Kai-ting of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Happy Valley Division
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-16 - Compliment on Police Officer of Airport District</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 
 
I am Japanese tourist who visited Hong Kong before.  On Feb 9, I lost my mobile phone in Hong Kong International Airport.  When I was at a loss and almost gave up, a police officer responded carefully and politely.  With his effort, my mobile phone was eventually found.  I appreciate his support and help so much.  His great job impressed me very much.

Kind regards, 
Shunsuke

Note : the officer praised in this letter is PC 50766 LAU Woon-shun of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Airport District   
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-14 - Compliment on Police Officer of Yau Ma Tei Division</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I would like to thank the Police Officer of Yau Ma Tei Division for their prompt response to a noise complaint I made.  It concerned a crazy man who regularly shouts from his window in our building late at night.  I have complained about this several times in the past few months, but when the police arrived, the shouting had stopped so no action ever got taken.

This time the same thing happened, but police officers showed the initiative to wait for a while in the stairwell to listen.  When the shouting started again, they visited the man's flat for further investigation.  Thanks for the help form those police officers.

Best Regards,
William

Note : One of the officer praised in this letter is PC 7556 LAU King-hin of Patrol Sub-unit 4, Yau Ma Tei Division  
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-13 - Compliment on Police Officer of Yuen Long Division</title><content>Dear Sir, 
 
I am writing to express my appreciation to the two police officers of Yuen Lung Division who helped to resolve the neighbourhood noise problem reported by me at a night of early February 2015. 
 
I live in Yuen Long Area.  Over the last whole month, there has been very annoying noise coming from the apartment upstairs.  I have sought help from the management office who has subsequently tried to contact the occupant of that apartment but all their effort was in vain as the occupant did not answer the door or the phone.  In desperation, I reported the problem to the police but much to my frustration, the noise stopped just before the police officers arrived.  After listening to my account of the problem, these two officers went up to the apartment upstairs to look into the problem.  Despite the fact that the noise had stopped, they managed to find that the source of the noise was an alarm device inside the apartment and at the end they successfully secured the agreement of the occupant to make appropriate adjustment to the device to reduce the noise level. 
 
Throughout the process, the officers were very polite and they displayed a high level of professionalism when handling the case.  They have not just done a commendable job but have also reinforced my positive impression of the Police Force.  For that, I would like to once again express my sincere appreciation.
 
Regards, 
Y C Lui
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-10 - Compliment on Police Officers of Airport District </title><content>In a morning of February 2015, I left my wallet on my way to airport in taxi.  I asked all around including information center but in vain.  Then, I went to police post and explained to a police officer about my situation.  He kindly helped me to find my lost item after calling taxi console.  Finally I found my wallet so I really want to compliment him on his sense of responsibility.  Thank You! 

Bets Regards, 
Mr. SUNG 

Note : the officers praised in this letter is PC 33222 CHEUNG Yau-hong of Patrol Sub-unit 4 , Airport District   

</content></item><item><title>2015-02-09 - Compliment on Police Officers of Cheung Sha Wan Division</title><content>Dear all, 

In a morning of February 2015, my colleague lost his wallet in the taxi.  As we had a night flight departing from HK the same day.  If he could not get the passport back, we would lose the flight.  Then we reported our case in the Police Force website (the electronic report room) and it was amazing.

We received the acknowledge email immediately after we reported the case online. Around a few minutes later, the Duty Officer of Cheung Sha Wan Police Station called back for case clarification.  Afterwards, I received several calls from them about the update.  Around one hour time, they told me the good news that the wallet had been found.  Finally, we went to the Cheung Sha Wan Police Station and collected the lost wallet.

All in all, the Duty Officer and their team are all very professional and polite.  In front of my colleague who came from Italy, I'm very proud to be a HongKonger as we have the best Police Force in the world.

Best Regards, 
Cathy 

Note : the officers praised in this letter are SSLT LEE Wai-wah, SGT 34747 WONG Yan-sang &amp; PC 51948 CHOI Sau-tak of DO Team 2 Cheung Sha Wan Division  

</content></item><item><title>2015-02-03 - Compliments on Police Officers of Hong Kong Island </title><content>Dear all, 

In an evening of January 2015, I lost my wallet in Hong Kong Island.  Fortunately, a woman police officer (Madam Yue) contacted me through telephone to ask me to take it back at Sai Wan Ho Police Station.  On the phone, she had been very courteous and informative, with all the patience in answering my questions.  Since I live in Kowloon, it took me quite a while to get myself to Sai Wan Ho Police Station, but she has been patiently waiting to settle my case.  After I reached the police station, Madam Yue diligently dealt with my lost and found case and had been a great help all along.  I apologise for any inconvenience caused to the police crew and Madam Yue.  I am sincerely grateful for their help, especially Madam Yue.  Please send my greatest gratitude to her and I wish her all the best ! Thank you ! 

Sonia  

Note: the officer praised in this letter is Woman Police Constable 56597 YUE King-pui of Traffic Investigation and Support Section, Hong Kong Island
</content></item><item><title>2015-02-01 - Compliments on Police Officers of Kowloon City District  </title><content>To whom it may concern,

I really say thank you to all the policemen who handled my case.  I am working at Cathay Pacific airways as a Japanese flight attendant.

In an afternoon of January 2015, I was taking a bus to the airport for my duty with my large suitcase from Hung Hum.  It was stolen by somebody right after the bus stopped at Whampoa Garden.  The bus driver and a passenger caught the thief and the case was taken over by a investigation unit of Kowloon City District.

The policemen explained to me that I needed to give a statement in the police office in English because I'm not Cantonese speaker.  My concern at that moment was whether I could make it to my flight or not, but they really helped me a lot.

They could finish all the paper works as soon as possible and helped me to arrange a taxi to my company.  I've been in HK around 9 years and it's the first time to encounter this kind of case.
HK is the safest city in the world because of Hong Kong Police, I can say.  Thank you so much.

Best Regards, 
Ms. Hana

</content></item><item><title>2015-01-30 - Compliments on Police Officers of Kwai Chung Division</title><content>Dear Sir /Madam, 

I am writing to compliment a police officer of Kwai Chung Division who had displayed his professionalism and helpfulness to the elderly. 

In an afternoon in January, when I was walking at Shek Yam Road, Kwai Chung, right opposite to the North Kwai Chung Market, I saw a police officer holding a wheel chair in which the elderly was sitting.  A relative of the elderly was talking to someone in the shop, which was around 3 metres far away.  Though the wheel chair might not be moved to the road, his initiative really impressed me. 

Regards, 

Mr. TANG 

Note: the officer praised in this letter is Police Constable 5144 LAI Chun-kit of Patrol Sub-unit 1, Kwai Chung Division.
</content></item><item><title>2015-01-28 - Compliments on Police Officers of Wan Chai Division </title><content>Dear Sir/ Madam,

I am writing to show my appreciation to several Wan Chai Division Police officers for their professionalism when handling my case.  I was assaulted by a client during working time, and the offender escaped from the incident location before I could even react.  I called 999 for police assistance and emergency medical service as soon as I recovered from tremendous dizziness.

I am surprised by how responsive our Police Force can be.  Two police officers of Wan Chai Police Station arrived at the scene within a few minutes.  They asked me to briefly describe the incident and the appearance of the escaped offender, and escorted me to the hospital.  After medical examination, I was called to give a statement for the incidence.  They explained well about the follow-up actions to me, and assured me that they would investigate the case.

To be honest, I thought that the issue would be forgotten but instead, Wan Chai Police called and told me that the offender had confessed about the attack.  I am more than happy that the issue can be resolved.  Thanks for your officers’ effort.   

Michael

Note: the officer praised in this letter is Police Constable 11155 LI Ka-ho and Police Constable 15126 TANG Man-kit of Patrol Sub-unit 1, Wan Chai Division.
</content></item><item><title>2015-01-13 - Compliments on Police Officers of Emergency Unit Hong Kong Island </title><content>Dearest Police officers of EU HK Island,

We reported a theft case of a missing laptop in an early morning in January 2015.  The members of the EU car were excellent and attentive to the case.

Due to the case itself, we were quite certain that it was more or less impossible to catch the thief.  To our utter surprise, with the outstanding work of the team, they had found our stolen laptop and arrested a suspect.

We wanted to take this opportunity to sincerely thank the team for their hard work and incredible attention to details, and their efficient work is beyond outstanding.

As a citizen in Hong Kong, I feel safe knowing that we have an amazing Police Force looking after us, and I am very proud to have you all as the representatives of this city.

Yours,
An extremely satisfied and grateful HK citizen

Angie 	

Note: the officer praised in this letter is Police Constable 54753 KU Tin, Police Constable 7390 TSE Yuk-ming and Woman Police Constable 8320 CHAN Ka-yee of Platoon 2 of Emergency Unit of Hong Kong Island.
</content></item><item><title>2015-01-05 - Compliment on Police Officer of Shatin District </title><content>I am a victim in a criminal case.  I would like to express our sincerest gratitude to a police officer, Mr. Liu of Sha Tin Police Station, for his help.  During the case investigation process, Mr. Liu has given utmost support and provided me with guidance. And, he was very patient in answering all of my questions and giving me feedbacks to address my concerns.

I am very impressed by his professionalism, and I cannot thank enough for his kindness.  Thanks !
  
Yours sincerely,
Mr. Lui 

Note : the officers praised in this letter is Constable 2033 LIU Seung-mo of District Investigation Team 5 Shatin District.
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-27 - Compliment on Police Officers of Kwun Tong Division </title><content>Dear Sir, 

I lost my wallet at Kwun Tong Area at the midnight on 2014-12-23.  Luckily, someone picked it up and sent it to Kwun Tong Police Station.  Then, a duty officer of Kwun Tong Police Station contacted me according to the information found from my belongings.

Eventually, I have gotten back my property without any loss.  I appreciate the effort of the aforesaid duty officer, he showed his patience and professional attitude to serve citizens like me.  Thank you! 

Mr. CHAN  
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-24 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Our dearest Police Force, 

As HK citizens, we take pride in all the pains you have bored for all of us.

Please extend our heartfelt thanks to everyone who was involved in clearing the illegally occupied roads.  We hope our frontline officers will recover from those unkind words made by the radicals.

Our prayers go with the Sergeant who is still admitted at ICU.  We are eager to see him back in the Force.

God bless you all!  Merry Christmas! 

Veronica 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-24 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

I would like to express that the Police must retain their dignity.  I am horrified to see the lack of respect for the Police from some of the protesters in the last 80 days or so.  To effectively maintain and respect law and order, the Police should charge the leaders of the illegal occupation, the protesters who attacked the Police and those who breached the law.  In any future demonstration, I think the majority of the public would understand if force had to be used when necessary.  I wish you the best of luck in your investigation and subsequent prosecution.

With kind regards, 

Man Fai 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-23 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear All, 

We salute Hong Kong Police Force for your professionalism, and brilliant performance in clearing up the illegal occupied areas!  

Best regards, 
 
A group of retired professionals
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-22 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sirs and Madams, 

Thank you so much for your contribution in maintaining law and order in this difficult period.  No other police forces in the world will have this level of tolerance, tact and empathy.  

A big salute to each and every one of you !

Carry on, you have many silent supporters behind.  

Best regards,

Jimmy
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-21 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sirs and Madams,

I would like to express my heartfelt thanks to the Hong Kong Police for their unfailing efforts in maintaining law and order despite the illegal occupation in the streets in the past few months.

As regards the use of force, I agree that it was inevitable and minimal.  We support Hong Kong Police anytime !  

Keep it up Hong Kong Police !

Steve

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-20 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,
 
Appreciate your restrain and discipline.  We are so proud of your team.  My American boss and his friends said Hong Kong Police is the best they have seen all over the world.

Best Regards,

Athena 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-19 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all Police officers,

Well done for all your sterling effort.  We appreciate very much your appropriate actions done for the resumption of original traffic network in all illegally occupied areas.

Last but not the least, hoping that the Police Sergeant admitted at ICU during operation can get well soon !

With best regards,

Mr. WONG 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-18 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all, 

Thank you Hong Kong Police for your hard work clearing the illegally occupied roads in Mong Kok, Admiralty and Causeway Bay finally!  For residents in mid levels and those minibus and taxi drivers, you have no idea how long we have been waiting for this day.

I hope the government won't let off those belligerent and law-breaking protestors easily after your hard work in the front line.  Those arrested on the spot deserve a criminal record or heavy fine for their selfish illegal road hijacking actions.  Without due punishments, the radicals will not learn that every action has a price to pay and will not think twice before they act rashly at the expense of other law-abiding citizens.

To those in the Police Force who had been putting up with myriads of verbal abuse and bullying by some law-breaking protestors, thank you for not quitting but soldiering on for the rest of us.  We appreciate your hard and long hours of work compounded by work frustrations.

You guys deserve a good long rest and family time with your love ! Thank You !

Yours faithfully, 

Jackson  
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-17 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir,

We are grateful for everyone in the Hong Kong Police Force in the past 79 days. Under such circumstances, your team has shown a great deal of discipline and professionalism.  Despite some of the negative media reports, there are still a lot of Hong Kong citizens who fully support the actions taken by the Hong Kong Police.

My thanks to your team! 

Mr. Lo 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-16 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

I just want to express my sincere thanks to all the police officers for your hard work to maintain law and order during the illegal occupation over the past two months.  Great job in clearing the illegally occupied sites with your professionalism.  Please do not let criminals get away or destroy our core values and legal system that have been built up over decades. 

Many people including myself can totally understand and empathize with the Police's role in this incident.  It is not because we personally know anyone working in the Force, but it is just common sense of many of us that the Police is doing everything right as "law enforcers".  I hope this small note can give some encouragement to the frontline officers.  Please know that you still have many of our support! 

We need the Police to protect our city and you are still one of the best Police Forces in the world in my opinion.  Thank you and please keep up the great work! 

Regards, 

Wendy
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-16 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sirs,
 
I write to express my gratitude to the Hong Kong Police Force for their efforts in handling the situation over the past two and a half months in the HKSAR.  The city experienced a very dangerous scenario where legal enforcement had been challenged and various public orders had been disregarded.
Being a member of the public, I was very anxious to see one of the fundamentals of our SAR that made us proud, the legal system, had been severely defied by some unlawful attempts.  Also, the livelihood and daily life of the majority of the public had been considerably affected by the illegal actions of some radicals such as blockage of main roads over such a prolonged period.

It was the Police Force that had displayed ultimate tolerance to provocations and outrageous actions, and managed to keep the situation under control.  Throughout several effective operations, the order of those unrest areas has been restored one after another and the traffic has resumed to its original state.  Not all of the operations were flawless, yet the public could see the professionalism displayed by the Force aiming to minimize any possible casualty involving any member of the public.  These have been proven to be successful and gladly the interests of the public have been well protected, and more importantly, law and order in Hong Kong have been restored.

I understand that throughout the difficult time the Police Force had been suffering from a lot both physically and mentally, in additional to the impact on the overall morale.   However, I am glad to see that all these did not affect the Force when performing their duties.  They are still one of the most efficient and professional services in the world.  Honestly, it would be hard to imagine how the situation would become without the decisive enforcement by the Force during this period.

At last, I would like to give my appreciation again to the Hong Kong Police Force, which they deserved, for all their efforts and dedications that have made Hong Kong one of the safest cities in the globe.

Thank you.

Yours sincerely,

Mr. Wan
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-15 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

I would like to thank the Hong Kong Police for clearing the illegally occupied sites in an orderly manner with the use of minimum force.  I am particularly impressed by the transparency of the operation so that everyone knows the timeline of the clearance, leaving little room for criticism.  I am sympathetic to those who have to deal with the "shopping mobs" in Mong Kok.  I truly hope these nonsensical activities will soon come to an end.  Last but not least, I wish a speedy recovery for the hospitalized police officer who collapsed during the operation.  Please keep up the good work.  The people in Hong Kong need and depend on you to maintain law and order in Hong Kong so that we can live in a safe environment. 

With warmest regards, 

Henrietta

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-15 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Hello Hong Kong Police, 

I wish to express my thanks and gratitude to all members of the Hong Kong Police for their high degree of integrity and restraint when dealing with some of the stubborn protestors in the past two months.

I truly believe that the Hong Kong Police is the best Police Force in the world and their methods and actions deserve the highest praise.

As the 5th generation of Hongkongers, I also believe that Hong Kong is one of the safest and most dynamic cities in the world due to the excellent policing developed over years.

Thank you Hong Kong Police for maintaining peace and order and enforcing and protecting the freedoms that we now enjoy.

THANK YOU.

Best Regards,  
Greene
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-14 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all, 

I am writing to show my support to the Hong Kong Police Force.  You have shown the world-class quality when facing the unparalleled demonstrations.  Your strategy was well applied yet politeness and great care were still shown.  Despite the provocative attacks, blames and insults, both tangibles and intangibles, you vowed to undertake relentlessly the mission to restore the law and order of Hong Kong.  I am really impressed.
 
Without you, Hong Kong could never be the Hong Kong it was used to be.  Hong Kong is still one of the safest places in the world.
 
Thank you very much!

Yours truly, 
 
Connie
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-14 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all Hong Kong Police officers,

We know that this is a very difficult day!  Eventually it comes to the day to clear the last illegally occupied area in Causeway Bay.  I am sure that you all will face a lot of difficulties when dealing with the protestors and students.

There are a lot of voices for or against the Police.  Some will say a lot of bad words about the Police.  So please stay open-minded for whatever kind of opinions as long as you know you are doing the right thing.

There is not much we can do but we can give you our warmest thanks.  We sincerely hope that nobody will get hurt and this illegal occupation will come to an end as soon as possible.

It doesn't mean it is the end even after tonight, and we all know that there may be other ways by which some of the students and protesters will continue to do against the government.  It will be tough.

Cheer Up!  Go, Go, Go!

We will always support you!

Take care and thanks.

Ms Cheung
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-13 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all,

I would like to show my appreciation to the contribution the Police Force has made to the Hong Kong society.  I would also like to express my support to the Police to enforce law and order.

The Police Force has shown a great deal of professionalism and work ethics when dealing with the recent prolonged protests while maintaining the law and order in the rest parts in Hong Kong.  Thank you very much for making Hong Kong a safe place.

I hope everything will turn out to be fine.  I also hope that the unfair public opinions and allegations regarding what you and your colleagues have done will not affect your spirit. 

Thank you very much again.

Kind regards, 

Mr. Yeung
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-12 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir and Madam,

We are totally in support of the Hong Kong Police Force to clear the blockages in Admiralty.  It has been too long to tolerate their illegal occupation.  We need to work, move and drive in Hong Kong freely as citizens of Hong Kong, not to be jeopardized by some of idealists, politicians and now mobs!

Please take care and avoid being hurt by the irrational protesters.  We trust you.

Thank you! 

Ms Tam
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-12 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Police officers, 
 
I write to thank you again for your tireless efforts in maintaining the law and order of Hong Kong especially in the past few months.
 
I hope you were not discouraged by those biased public opinions.  You guys have done a great job.  Please continue to stay strong, tough and responsible being in such uncivilized warfare.  There are some evil-minded people trying to twist lies into truths.  Their objectives are so obvious and not going to succeed.  
 
Please continue to do what needed to be done.  The Hong Kong people support you and thank you very much for your tireless efforts.

Yours sincerely,

Heidi 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-12 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To all our friends of the Hong Kong Police Force,
 
We salute you for all you have done to protect our city from being taken over by part of the community, and for the peace, law and order your gave us.  Special thanks for your clearance operation in Admiralty areas.
 
We fully support your brave deeds and we would like to tell you that we are very proud of you.
 
A big THANK YOU from the bottom of our hearts!
 
With our sincerest gratitude and appreciation, keep up the spirit!
 
Warmest regards,
 
Louisa and family
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-12 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir,

You are doing the right thing to clean up the illegal occupied areas in Central, and also later Causeway Bay!

Some of those people in the Occupy Central are far too loud and absurd.  They are so arrogant and only shouted for their ideals that they totally forgot the well-beings of Hong Kong people.  We have the right to lead normal lives - walking, driving and shopping in Hong Kong....  Now that we are cut off from this freedom!

Please do whatever you are legitimated to do.  We support Hong Kong Police!

Best Regards,

HK resident Ms. Lu
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-12 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,

Very glad to see you finally clean up the illegal occupation.  We need our roads and our lives back!

Thanks!  Thanks!  Thanks!

Best Regards, 

Tina
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-11 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear PPRB Team, 

Thank you so much for the whole Police Force in restoring the peace and order in Admiralty today and all the hard work in other areas in Hong Kong.  We have been supporting you all throughout the past 75 days.  We understand that you have been facing immense pressure from the press and public, but your team is very professional and dedicated.  I did stop by to cheer up and give compliment to the policemen on the street, and I would like to express our appreciation for all your contribution as well.
 
Many of my friends and I disagree with anyone who breaches the law in the name of democracy and sacrificing other’s right of using the roads.  Your work is very challenging, meaningful and important, and please do keep it up.
 
Stay Healthy, Happy and Safe!  Have a Merry Christmas! 
 
Best regards, 

Fiona &amp; Parkco 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-11 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police Force,

Thank you very much for your professional approach to clean up the Occupy Admiralty.  We are getting to the end of the tunnel.

Take care and all the best.

Wishing you all a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year.

Mr. Ko
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Police,

Thank you for the definitive action to clean up the Occupy Central mess tomorrow! The roads in Admiralty and Causeway Bay are so important in Hong Kong Island, and the illegal occupation affects millions of Hong Kong citizens' daily life - so ridiculous and so inconvenient!

We are looking forward to see this rectified.

Thank you very much.

Ailsa 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,

Thank you very much for all of your efforts and hard work in handling the illegal occupation in some areas in Hong Kong.  Recently, the Police have faced tremendous pressure and comments on their way of handling the matter on some occasions, but I strongly believe in your professionalism and I support the way you handled all these.  I would like to express my sincere and strong support to you all.  Please continue to handle the event with pride and effort as always. 
Best Regards,

Berry
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear the Police Force, 

I would like to express my gratitude to the Hong Kong Police Force for all the hard work you do – maintaining law and order in Hong Kong in the face of the illegal occupations.  From the news, I know that the Police Force will clear the illegally occupied sites in Admiralty on Thursday.  Please take good care of yourselves and I wish you success!  Thank you once again for protecting Hong Kong and defending the rights and freedom of the majority of Hong Kong people.

Maria 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

Thanks for your dedication to your duties.  You all have faced a lot of pressure and difficulties in handling all the illegally occupied areas involved in the Occupy Central movement.

Please know that we all support you.  Your performance at work shows your patience, love, respect and professionalism.  We all thank you for your great work. Add Oil.

Hin 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all, 

I am appreciating and affirming the Police who take up the responsibility of handling the illegal occupying activities in Central.  You have done a good job and you are supported by every normal citizen.

To all police officers, add oil !

Yours sincerely, 

Maggie 

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

Great to have the decision and action to clear up the illegally occupied areas in Admiralty!

It is going to be hard work, but we, the citizens, are looking forward.  It has been a long long time we have suffered from the road blockage! 

Thank you!  Please take care as it will be rainy and cold.

Yours truly, 

Taune
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To whom it may concern,

It's very grateful for the police force to have devoted their best endeavour to protect the best interest of Hong Kong citizens in the disturbing Occupy Central activities.

Keep it going and you will always have the support of the majority of HK citizens and mine.  Kindly pass this thankful message to every member of the police force whenever possible.

Best Regards, 

Edmond 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all, 

I knew thousands of Hong Kong citizens had expressed gratitude for the service of the HKPF.  My wife and I would like to join these people.  Thank you HKPF for your excellent work in dealing with the students and protesters participating in the Occupy movement.  Please keep on your good work and be assured of our continuous support.

Sincerely yours,

Mr. &amp; Mrs. Fong 

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-09 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all members of the Hong Kong Police,

On behalf of my family, I wish to give our deepest gratitude for the hard work everyone of you has done in safeguarding us, the peace-loving Hong Kongers, against some of the rogue-demonstrators.  

You have shown to the world the highest professionalism and the greatest perseverance over this long and tiring struggle which rarely happens in HK.  We are proud of you.  Please keep up the spirit as you can be assured that the vast majority of Hong Kongers are behind you.

Thank you and wish you all good luck and good health.

Leonard 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-09 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police Force, 

I am writing to express my sincere and heartfelt gratitude to all of you for your efforts in maintaining the law and order of Hong Kong during the Occupy Central movement.  Your professionalism, your patience, and your perseverance are highly praised.  We are proud to have you around!

Hope this mail can encourage your spirit a bit.  We are with you and back you up with prayers and concerns!  Add oil Hong Kong Police Force!

Sincerely yours,

Miss Miriam

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-08 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

I wish to express my appreciation to the Police Force for their efforts in dealing with the students and people occupying Mong Kok and Central areas.  The policemen have shown remarkable patience and displayed true professionalism.  Well done.

You have the full support from all the law-abiding citizens.  Thank you for your excellent service.

Alice
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-07 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,

Officers on duty are highly courageous and disciplined.  The force used is minimal and controlled.  Many officers were injured and I wish them speedy recovery.  Violent protestors are totally unacceptable and use of force to disperse them is necessary.  I, as a citizen of Hong Kong, fully support and appreciate the work of the Hong Kong Police. 

Best wishes to Hong Kong,

Sandra
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-05 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,

Like the majority of Hong Kong citizens, I support the police action to disperse the rioters in Admiralty and Mong Kok recently.  Despite the protests led by some student representatives and pro-democracy parties, your action to restore the social orders in Hong Kong is absolutely right.

Again, it is only a small group of students and rioters to organise the protests to hurt the society.  Please keep up with your good work and spirit.  You have support from the majority of us!

Mr. Ho
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-05 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all,

The past few weeks were the darkest time in Hong Kong during which so many people have violated laws.  Police were being treated in an unfair way by some protestors.  As a Hong Kong citizen, I really appreciate the hard work done by the Hong Kong Police.  Please keep it up.  Many Hong Kong citizens support all of you.

Thank you for your hard work.

A Hong Kong citizen
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all,

This is to express my continuous support to the Hong Kong Police.  I think that the current political environment has been dominated by some people with no sense, but I believe this will come to an end soon.  Please keep your patience, and always bear in mind that you have the support from most people in Hong Kong.
 
I am proud of Hong Kong Police Force, and grateful to you all and your supporting families.

Lastly, please send my highest regards to the officers who got hurt, and wish them speedy recovery.

Yours truly,

Clara
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear police officers,

I feel so sorry about what has happened these 2 months.  My family strongly support the Hong Kong Police.  I think what happened last night was riot.  As a Hong Kong citizen, I am angry and I fear those who are against the law.

Please just do your job and arrest the people who are against the law.  Once again, fully support the Hong Kong Police!

Best Regards,

Jenny
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sirs,

Thanks for all of your effort and hard work to enforce the lawful environment in Hong Kong.  You all get our support for it.  This is a tough situation.  We stand behind you.  For those who broke the law for whatever reason, this is not what we want.  God bless all of you and protect you from getting any hurt at work.

Best regards,

Monica

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-03 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Some of the participants of Occupy Central movement in Hong Kong are not protesters but indeed rioters.  They do not respect laws and orders, do not respect the wishes of the majority of Hong Kong people, and do not respect our highly reputable policemen and policewomen in Hong Kong.  Again in my eyes, they are merely lawbreaking rioters who go around destroying Hong Kong.  Those behaviours should be handled with necessary force.  I have high expectation of you, the Hong Kong Police, getting the job done well in confronting the riots and arresting the law breakers.  

Thank you very much for your bravery to protect Hong Kong people and our properties.  I am writing it just as the concern for our future only.  All the best and may God be with you all.  

Thanks &amp; Regards,
 
Mr. Ho 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-03 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Police, 

Thank you again for maintaining the peace in Hong Kong.  We really appreciate you!  I feel that I need to write to encourage all of you.  

I really admire all your colleagues who braved the fight last night against the hooligans, but I am so sorry that many officers got injured as well.  I pray that they will get well soon and be honoured for all that they have done.  

All of your colleagues have worked really well in the midst of chaos.  Well done.  Be assured of my prayers for all of you and peace for Hong Kong, 

Blessings,

Mrs Tang	
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-03 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear All, 

Thanks for all the hard work.  I completely support the police action in clearing up the road.  Please continue your hard work.

Helen
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-02 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To everyone of the Hong Kong Police Force,
　
I know this letter might not mean a lot, but I just want to thank everyone of the Hong Kong Police Force for staying professional and sticking to your posts to keep our lives and properties safe and sound throughout this turmoil.
　
I just want to let you know that there are many, many people in Hong Kong who are 200% supportive of your effort in trying to restore the order in this city.  Hong Kong is currently suffering from a political war with different stakeholders trying to fool the public for their own gain.　
　
In the incident of using tear gas, no matter what we saw on the television, what we learnt from the rumors spread on the internet, or even from those who claimed that they were at the scenes, no one on this earth will be able to see "everything" and knowing "all the facts" in such a chaotic situation.　 There have been plenty, and will have even more criticisms by the Occupy Central participants, politicians or different stakeholders against the HKPF on the media.　 We need the HKPF to be here to ensure the order of the society to be restored.　 Without your professionalism and endurance, we will lose this place that all of us have built throughout these years in the blink of the eyes.　 
　
A lot of us know and can imagine what each of you is going through physically, psychologically, mentally and spiritually throughout this ordeal.  Believe me, there are plenty of us who are extremely grateful that all of you are sticking to your posts, and we truly wish we could do more.　　 
　
Once again, I just want to say that we are grateful and we are indebted to all of you for being able to live in an orderly environment.　 Please do not give up.　 We have your back as you have ours.

Woods
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-01 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

I am from Germany, and I have lived in Hong Kong for 9 years.  I am now a permanent resident, and I love this city with all my heart.  It saddens and grieves me to see the irresponsible, irrational and unlawful behavior of the protesters throughout the past weeks.  Not only me, but everyone I talked to agrees that what some of the protesters were doing is not only disruptive and troublesome for the innocent people in Hong Kong, but also highly harmful to Hong Kong as a city.

At the same time I want to express my deep gratitude and respect for the Hong Kong Police.  I know that many policemen have worked overtime under very difficult conditions and accusations during the past days, but please don't be discouraged.  We really need the help of Hong Kong Police to ensure the safety of Hong Kong citizens, and I am very thankful for your professional work.

Meanwhile, I will continue to pray that this crisis situation can be brought to a peaceful and reasonable conclusion as soon as possible.

Honson

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-01 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all,

You are doing an exceptional job given the extreme circumstances.  You should be proud of yourselves and contrary to the various protest groups, you have the support and gratitude from the majority of Hong Kong people.  Stay safe and we all look forward to the end of the crisis.  Hopefully, a compromise can be reached for all Hong Kong people.

Rick 

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-01 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>In view of the outstanding performance and hard work of the Police Force to resume the public order in Hong Kong, I would like to express my thanks and support to you all for your remarkable hard working and excellent performance in handling the Occupying Central illegal movement.
 
Well Done.
 
Sincerely yours,
A citizen who loves Hong Kong

</content></item><item><title>2014-12-01 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I am here to express my sincere gratitude to the HK Police Force in assisting in the clearance exercise of the illegal occupation in Mong Kok and in handling the chaos there these days to protect the citizens and the law and order of HK! 

It cannot be described in words how I appreciate your efforts and contribution to HK since the illegal Occupy Central movement began in late Sep!

My family and I are proud of you all with heartfelt thanks!  Hope the order in our city can resume shortly!  Please send my support to you all and your families!

Cheers and take care! 

Fai’s family 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-01 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I have recently seen a lot of videos and clips about the Occupy Mong Kok incident. 

Most, if not all, people agree that the whole Police Force have consistently demonstrated their patience and efforts when carrying out their duties.  You are highly appreciated.  Most, if not all, people in the world know that Hong Kong Police are very professional and disciplined.  We would like to see all of you to keep up with the good work in this difficult period. 

As some people and media have been seeking every chance to deepen the grievances in Hong Kong, please stay calm and have a clear mind at all times.  We share the pressure that the police have been facing.  I really hope that the issue can be resolved as soon as possible.

Yours truly, 

David 
</content></item><item><title>2014-12-01 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all members of the Police Force, 
  
Don’t get upset by some of the negative media reports.  The majority of Hong Kong People support you. Please use any appropriate force to stop the crime.

Wish all Police officers health and happiness forever.

Regards,

Sandra 

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-30 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir,

I would like to express my sincere support to the Hong Kong Police for your effort in maintaining the law and order in Hong Kong.

Despite the rude and criminal-like behaviour of some dissidents and protestors, I could see the Police in Hong Kong possess an extremely high degree of professionalism.

I truly understand your sufferings during this difficult period and I send my best wishes to everyone in the Police Force and also their families.

With my best regards,

Nick 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-30 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police Force,

Salute everyone of you for your recent hard work in enforcing the law and order in Hong Kong!

The riot which has happened recently is terrible.  As a Hong Kong citizen, I am so proud that we have an extremely professional and respectable team of police officers to safeguard and protect us against the rioters.

I am sorry to learn that some policemen had been hurt in the previous operations.  I hope that those who got hurt will have a speedy recovery and wish you all safe and sound in any future operation.

With Best Wishes,

Dick 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-29 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

My sincere gratitude to the entire Hong Kong Police Force,

The immense duty and responsibility you are carrying out is beyond imagination of a normal citizen like me.  Salute you all from the bottom of my heart.  Give you my huge respect for the endeavour of the officers on selfless duty to serve the public for their interests.  It's total devotion and commitment of oneself to serve people; it's a great commitment of a person; it’s the highest self-discipline one can achieve.  To me, it is an impossible human act.

Without your uniform, you are just like me, a normal person living in Hong Kong with a job and your own family and friends; You are just trying to make a life worthwhile, meaningful and happy, and giving support to your own family.

I wish you all the best of luck all the time.  Nothing else I can express but my most sincere gratitude.  Thank you all. 

Yours faithfully,

A Hong Konger
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-29 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Police officers, 
 
Having been a Hong Kong resident for 20 years, I want to express my thanks and appreciation for the hard work all of you have done.

There is a deep respect and admiration for all that you do for Hong Kong.

Thank you!

Anna 

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-29 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Just want to express my deepest appreciation for your efforts in dealing with the recent riots and your patience when dealing with some irrational protestors.

Support from a humble citizen

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-29 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I greatly respect and appreciate what the Police Force are doing to ensure the safety and well-being of Hong Kong people during the Occupy Central movement.

Please feel free to let me know if there is anything I can do to help or support you.

Yours truly, 

May
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-29 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear officers,

I'm writing you to show my support and appreciation to your team.  Thank you so much for your endeavour during this time.  Your professional performance have impressed every calm resident in HK.  All the best!  The bright days are coming after the dark! 

All the best,

A HK resident
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-29 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,

I just want to take a few minutes to write and express my most sincere gratitude to you.  I am not a protestor or an anti-protestor, but I am a Hong Kong citizen like you.  And like you, I want my home to be home.  I will never be able to fully comprehend the stress and difficulties you have faced or those you are currently facing.  I will also never know the unbiased truth regarding the whole Occupy Central movement, but I know that whatever the outcome is, you will strive to uphold the justice and peace in Hong Kong and for that, I thank you.

Thank you for standing in the rain, under the sun or clouds in the past days.
Thank you for protecting both the protestors and the anti-protestors.
Thank you for making sure that I can cross the streets safely.
Thank you for remaining professional.
Thank you for being patient.
Thank you for setting an example of orderly conduct.
Thank you for putting your own opinions aside but our safety first.
Thank you for staying with the people even when you are thinking of your family at home.
Thank you for not giving inappropriate remarks. 
Thank you for not taking the protest personal against your work. 
Thank you for your sweat, toil, tears, or even blood. 
Thank you to your family for their sacrifice. 

Keep up the good work.

Best Regards, 

Jeff 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-28 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Hello Sir/Madam, 

I am a Singaporean living with my family here for the past ten years during which we have come to love this great city very much. 

Watching the protests on TV in the past weeks, I am writing to compliment the Hong Kong Police Force for your restraint and effort to keep the peace with these, sometimes, violent protesters.

I fully support the use of pepper sprays and the firing of tear gas.  In our office debates, I often posed the questions of, ‘What would be the outcome if the Police did not do what they did?  Would any government in the world allow these mobs to damage these important government buildings?’

Please share my salute to the whole Police Force and keep up with the good work.  There are many, like me, who are fully supportive of your efforts!  All the best!

Margaret 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-28 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all, 

My wife and I are Hong Kong citizens currently residing in Shanghai.  The recent Occupy Central movement is truly disheartening where protesters choose to use methods that threaten the law and order in Hong Kong.  A movement that lacks planning, control, and contingency plan are no better than thugs at play.

Despite being thousands of miles away we want to convey our sincere support and appreciation to the Hong Kong Police Force for all that you've done, including using necessary force to maintain the order in Hong Kong!

Go Hong Kong!  Go Hong Kong Police!  Please know that there are many people like us who are behind your back!

Sincerely, 

Benson 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-28 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear HK Police, 

My heartfelt thanks for your great effort in handling Occupy Central.  I admire your sound judgement and professional skills.  I believe that the use of tear gas is appropriate.

I hope Hong Kong will become peaceful soon!

Best regards, 

Victor 

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-28 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all Police officers, 

Your performance and efforts are so impressive.  In the past days, you have shown me and the other people in Hong Kong that you are professional, tolerant, patient, and determined to uphold the rule of law of Hong Kong.

Your efforts will be remembered in every heart of Hong Kong people.  I totally agree that you performed your duty in accordance with the law of Hong Kong and did not use excessive force on protesters.  Please accept my heartfelt thank.

Yours truly,

Johnny 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-28 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all, 

I am writing to make you aware of the excellent service that Hong Kong Police have provided to Hong Kong Citizens.  You have showed the professionalism and full understanding of your roles and responsibilities when handling the Occupy Central movement.  Hong Kong Police have been giving us tremendous help with this.  I would like to express my gratitude not only to you but also the Force as a whole.

Hong Kong citizens need you and Hong Kong Police to protect our lives and property, and meanwhile avoid violence against others.  Once again, thank all Hong Kong policemen.  Let us build a peaceful Hong Kong!

Best Regards,

Kitty   
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-27 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sirs,

Thanks so much for your contribution to Hong Kong.

There are no more words that can express my gratitude.  Keep on your excellent jobs
Support is here!

Chris
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-27 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Hello HK Police Force,  

More than 60 days have passed, and the illegal protesters are still causing nuisance and inconvenience to the general public, not to mention the losses incurred by the retailers. 

Seeing the events unfolding on TV, the newspapers and Facebook, I have a few comments:

That the protesters are now more daring in challenging the rule of law that HK so proudly uphold with their verbal abuses, challenging police with provocative acts and causing traffic obstructions with their sporadic acts of road blockages. 

It is time to act decisively for the citizens' patience and for the well-being of the society. 

I am fully supportive of all your efforts.  I hope the time is now to act decisively to clear the streets of these illegal protesters and to bring them to justice. 

Regards, 

Mr. Teo
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-27 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam of the Hong Kong Police Force,

All my friends would like to express our appreciation for what you all have done so far to ease out the occupying activities. 

We are very proud of our Hong Kong Police, you are the BEST in the world!
Thank you again.

Mabel 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-27 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To all the members of the Police Force,

I fully support the Police to use proper force to maintain the law and order of Hong Kong.  I really appreciate the hard work performed by all the members of the Police Force during these 60 odd days.

Please keep up the spirit as the stability of Hong Kong depends on you.

Thank you!

Yours sincerely,

Johnson 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-27 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sirs,

Thank you for your hard work.  You have displayed the highest professional standard in handling the demonstrators.  You have done all you can to try to restore law and order.  You have earned my respect.

Regards,

Rita

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-27 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Just want to say thank you to all members of the Police Department in Hong Kong, especially the policemen working hard to maintain law and order in Hong Kong during these few weeks of Occupying Central.  You have my support and heartfelt thanks.  Salute the best police!

A Hong Kong citizen
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-27 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 
 
Thank you for what you have done, particularly for clearing the roadblocks and restoring the public order.  I believe in "rule by the law", thereby no one, including those who think that they "represent the justice", is above the law.  Roads are designed for vehicles but not for pedestrians or campers.  Protestors should stay away from the roads.  I trust that most of you share this belief.  

Best Regards, 

Mr. HO 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To all HK police, 

Support all of you to carry out the hardest duty for the safety of the public and the order of the society! 

Yours sincerely,

Ms. Lau 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam,

I am writing to express my most heartfelt gratitude to the Hong Kong Police Force for your selfless contribution to maintain stability and order in Hong Kong.  In this recent few weeks, Hong Kong has endured unprecedented challenge.  Some unlawful citizens have occupied major roads of business areas and brought unexpected detrimental effects and damages to the harmony and economy of our home town.  Officers of our police force need to endure humiliation, physical assault and psychological stress in handling the situation.  I must say that I am really proud of our force in your endurance and professionalism.  I am sure that the vast majority of Hong Kong citizens feel the same and will offer their full support to the Police. Thank you officers!  Your excellent work is appreciated! 

Last but not least, I would salute to every members of the Hong Kong Police Force. Hope my little message can spread to the heart of every officer in Hong Kong Police Force!  

Thank you very much for your attention.

Yours sincerely,

Mr. Ku 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Police Officers,  

I am a resident of HK although I am away at the moment.  I would just like to give you my support for your difficult job in dealing with the protesters.  I think you have showed courage, tolerance and restraint in a very difficult situation and I would support your action in bringing normal life back to HK people. 

Monica 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear members of the Hong Kong Police Force, 

I and my family, my staff, and my friends give you our utmost support and faith.  Thank you for courageously facing and dealing with these difficulties protecting the real interest of the Hong Kong Public. 

Best wishes to you all. 

Daniel 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all, 

Hong Kong citizens support and appreciate the Hong Kong Police Force.  Please accept our most sincere appreciation from the bottom of our hearts.  Keep up the great work!  THANK YOU!!

Mandy 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear HK Police, 

I am not a resident of Hong Kong anymore.  I migrated to Australia in 1987, and have been residing in Brisbane since then.  Even though I have migrated, I still consider Hong Kong as my home and China as my country.  The Occupy Central Movement make me very worried about the future of HK and deep in my heart I know without Hong Kong Police’s presence, the situations will deteriorate really quick.

The recent clashes between the so-called ‘freedom fighters’ and the HK Police have really triggered my nerve.  I feel sorry for the Police in Hong Kong being put under such a huge duress.  I take my hat off to your professionalism and tolerance towards some of the unruly mobs. 

Some of the so-called ‘freedom fighters’ assert themselves as non-violent and peace loving groups, but they are none of these at all.  They employ psychological violence of abusive language and condescending indifference to challenge your patience and tolerance.  They wear you out both physically and mentally with their guerrilla warfare tactics.  These unruly mobs know full well that you cannot react to their senseless behaviours because you are wearing the uniform of the Hong Kong Police.  I despise these unruly mobs.

I give the Hong Kong Police my full support because I know you are the BEST POLICE FORCE in the world.  No other Police Forces can be as patient, tolerant and professional as you are.  I know every Hong Kong having migrated to Brisbane support Hong Kong Police unconditionally.
 
Regards,
 
Ms. LEUNG
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir, 

I am writing to express my support to the HK Police Force at this critical moment of HK.  I appreciate very much that the HK Police has always been contributing to the safety and order of HK.  I understand this is a very tough time for the HK Police right now as you have to deal with unlawful behaviours.  While it is difficult to enforce the law, I hope, with your professionalism, the HK Police will be able to handle it well and continue to earn the respect from HK people.  Thank you very much for all the efforts of all Hong Kong policemen! 

Mr. NG 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To all policemen in Hong Kong, please do not get frustrated.  I think most of the Hong Kong people support you.

Kind regards,

Janet 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all,

Recently I know you are all just doing your jobs.  Since there are some people from the Occupy Central movement who are causing all the damage, it is unfair to make you the scapegoat for the whole situation.  You are just trying to protect the silent majority who didn't ask for all this.  Please ignore the citizens who are criticizing you.  Keep doing what you are doing because you are the only influential group in HK who are doing the right things.  Remember that you are doing nothing wrong, so don't allow the media to influence your thoughts.  Hereby I express my utmost support to your cause.  Thanks for doing what you are doing.

Sincerely,

Connie 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-26 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam,

I am writing to express my appreciation and support for the great work of HK Police in righteously maintaining law and order, and protecting life and property.  Handling massive protests and illegal occupants of roads are extremely difficult and challenging. The hard work, patience, courage and devotion of HK Police members are highly commendable. 

Every law-abiding citizen in the city is so proud to have such an elite Police Force. Please let your frontline officers know they are not alone as my thoughts are with them.  Keep up the great work. 

Best regards,

Teresa 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-25 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>My dear policemen in the front line, 
 
Hong Kong people will always remember you and the hard times you have gone through in these days.  Many of us would like to join you and clear the protesters but if ordinary people approach the sites, we will only add more burden to you.  Pray that you will walk through these stormy days safely.  My heart goes to everyone of you, taking long shifts, with little rest hours, defending the law and order.  The most painful thing is that you have to fight with the most unreasonable crowds, for a cause which has turned to be absolutely worthless.  Please keep up your spirit, my dear policemen in the front line.  Just as the song written by your colleagues – “be determined, be strong”.  You will never be crushed and you will always keep your head up, for what you believe in.  Pray for your safety, pray for your strength.

Best Regards,

Roy
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-23 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>What I have seen in the Occupy Central event is that Police are protecting Hong Kong citizens.  No matter how bad the situation has become, you have demonstrated your commitment and strength to us.  I want you to know that I have never had any doubt in you.  It is ridiculous and childish to think that Police is the enemy.  I salute you once again.

Yours truly, 

Maggie
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-21 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear officers,

I'm writing you to show my support and appreciation to your team.  Thank you so much for your endeavor during this time.  Your professional performance has impressed every calm resident in HK.  

All the best,

HK residents
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-20 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Police,

I am writing to make you aware of the excellent assistance that Hong Kong Policemen have given to Hong Kong Citizens.  They showed the professionalism and full understanding of their roles and responsibilities when handling several occupations.  Hong Kong Policemen have given us a tremendous help with this.  I would like to express my gratitude not only to you and your department but also to the team as a whole. 

Hong Kong citizens need you and HK Policemen to protect our lives and properties and avoid violence against others.  Once again, thank all Hong Kong Policemen.  Let us build a peaceful Hong Kong!

Best Regards, 

Tom
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-20 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To all the Police officers in Hong Kong, 

I understand for the previous weeks, all Police officers are put under tremendous physical and psychological pressure. 

First of all, I have to stress and make sure that your colleagues understand on Sept 28 when the tear gas was deployed, the Police Force did the RIGHT thing.  Emotionally difficult for Hong Kong, your team defended the attempted illegal occupation of the Central Government Complex.  Protestors violated the law, the Police Force exercised its given power to enforce law and social stability.  I got it, and as a citizen I will also try to let people understand the situation.  Please do not let your fellow Police officers doubt the righteousness of your action.  It is unfair to judge Police action on political grounds, and to misjudge the righteousness of your action. 

I am also sorry that your officers are constantly under verbal abuse by certain sectors of the society.  Thank you for your tolerance in this difficult situation!  Thank you for not giving up on us and Hong Kong!  Some of us do not understand how lucky we are to have such a professional Police Force protecting us every day, but many of us do!  Many of us have tremendous respect for you officers BECAUSE of the current situation, and you should continue to serve with PRIDE!

Supporter of Hong Kong Police, 

Alan 

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-20 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>My family, friends, and I would like to commend the whole Hong Kong Police Force on their absolutely professional actions in restoring law and order in the Occupy Central incident.

We also saw broadcast of press conferences the Force held with the Fire Services Department. Chief Superintendent Hui of PPRB gave us clear explanation of the considerations behind the tactics taken.  We fully understand that some members of the public challenged the Force's decisions.  Those "complaints" were simply unreasonable and fault-finding. 

We would like to end this note with the following message: Well done, Officers!!!  We believe the majority of the community appreciate your work and want to give you our full support. Please continue to protect Hong Kong.

Yours Sincerely,

Ian   
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-20 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear officers,

I am an ordinary Hong Kong citizen, a homemaker, not a shop owner or businessman.  Along with many other citizens, I too, support our Hong Kong Police regarding the way of handling the Occupy Central activists.  In my opinion, Hong Kong Police has been very soft to the protesters and always polite.  I have been living in the UK for many year, and Hong Kong Police are just world-class.  I am proud of them.

Some of the protesters are slowly turning into hooligans.  We shall see who was right and who was wrong.  Hong Kong Police, we, the sensible ones, support you.  Do Not Back Off!
Hong Kong people need you!

Best Regards,

Mr. Hung 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-16 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>All members of Hong Kong Police,

I am writing to give encouragements to all HK Police officers to continue to serve our community with pride.  I sincerely appreciate and salute all HK Police officers for your professionalism and perseverance particularly in these hard days and nights from late September until now.  Thank you so much!

Hong Kong Citizen,

Johnny 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-16 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

I would like to express my most sincerely and respect to Hong Kong Police Force for the work controlling the illegal occupation.

Those unlawful and selfish activities have created a lot of inconvenience to a lot of people.  
Just a short word that I appreciate the work that Police Force has done and I will support the Police to recover this situation. 

Best Regards, 

Dickson
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-15 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear HK Police,

My continuous support and thanks to all your efforts to maintain law and order in HK.
You got all my support to use appropriate force to clear all the blockades that are creating tremendous inconvenience to other law abiding citizens.  We are also entitled to civil rights to lead a normal life.  Those people creating this turmoil are only a small crowd compared with the mass majority, so 'enough is enough' to those activists.  I have total trust in the discernment of the HK Police to act appropriately to rectify this situation.
My heartfelt thanks to you all!

HK Citizen

Mandy 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-14 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>In view of the recent chaotic situation caused by a small group of people with special political objectives in mind, I know that you all have been given a very difficult task to try to maintain peace and order in HK whilst being attacked physically and verbally by those people.  Don't be upset!  We, the majority of the HK people, are on your side and do appreciate your hard works very much.  We all support you.  I would like to express my gratitude to all in the Police here.  Thank you very much!

Sincerely,

David  
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-13 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>2014-11-13 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force 

I would like to express my appreciation to the Police officers, especially those on the front line, during this difficult time.  You have been patient, tolerant, and doing the best you can.  It is very hard and you can get hurt by this.

I have seen some protestors doing all they can to provoke the Police officers, and shouting at them.  People who only watch the news on TV do not see this.  

Thank you for doing a good job which is very difficult.  I know this is very stressful.  Please hold on.  I am sure many Hong Kong people are behind you. 

Your Supporter,

Jacky
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-12 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Regarding the Occupy Central (and now, Occupy HK), and as a long-time resident here, I compliment the Force for your compassion, restraint, and duty to keep the peace and order of HK. 

I was watching the live TV on Sep 30 afternoon and saw the unfolding of events that led to the use of pepper sprays and firing of the tear gas canisters.  These are the right actions to cool down the violent actions of these protesters.  The Force did the right thing and should be proud of yourselves.  This short statement is from someone who wishes HK well and would like to see a prosperous city.  All the best!

Yours truly, 

Kevin
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-12 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Hong Kong Police has demonstrated their professionalism in taking care of the riot.  Despite the stream of profanity from the protesters, day in and day out the Police work round the clock to restore law and order in Hong Kong.  I really appreciate the persistence and proficiency of the Police in Hong Kong.  As a local citizen of Hong Kong, I am glad to have such a strong team to work for us.

Best Regards, 

Kay 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-11 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear all, 

I just want to express my heartfelt gratefulness to the Hong Kong Police Force, especially to all the frontline officers who have been involved in the Occupy Central protest.  DON'T DESPAIR.  You all have done an excellent job and have been the most professional.  Your unreserved effort to serve the HK community will not be in vain.  Time will tell and some people will eventually learn to appreciate your value. 

Yours truly, 

Sandy 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-11 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police, 

I actually live in Sydney, and I am planning to move to Hong Kong to get married with my boyfriend who is a citizen of Hong Kong, but the protest made me having second thought about relocating... When I saw the photos of you doing a brilliant job under this extreme circumstance, I'm simply touched.  Talking from experience, Sydney Police Force won't be so restrained and tolerant as you are.  So, Hong Kong Police, thank you so much for rebuilding my confidence and please be proud of yourself.  It takes great courage and bravery to do what you are doing, and last but not least, please take care.

Best Regards, 

Grace

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,

You all have done a great job.  Despite this very difficult time, you have handled all situations in a very professional manner.  All the people in Hong Kong are very grateful to you and you are the best!  Please be patient and Hong Kong will shine again.

Your Supporter, 

Mabel 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir, 

Thank you for enforcing law and order in Hong Kong demonstrating the highest professional standard.  I also support HK Police to take necessary actions to take back our streets.

Citizen, 

Janet 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-10 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Police Force,

With my deepest heartfelt thanks and appreciation for your professionalism, restraint and tolerance these days.  Keep it up and never give up!  Thank You! 

Best Regards,

Jay 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-09 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear all Police officers, 

May I express my heartfelt thanks and appreciation to all of you.  Your steadfast patience in recent adversity really impressed all Hongkongers!  You are all doing a splendid job.  Keep up the good work.  Pray for you and may the grace and love of GOD Jesus Christ be with you always! 

A Hong Kong resident,

Joyce Fong
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-09 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear HK Police,

I have lived in HK for 7 years, and just became a permanent resident.  I have witnessed civil unrest in the UK from the Moss Side riots of 1981, through the Poll Tax riot of 1990, and the more recent days of rage. 

It seems very clear from watching what has taken place over the last few weeks in HK that you have shown very significant restraint compared with the Police in other countries.

I strongly commend you for this.  It makes me feel happier to live in HK.  I never thought I'd ever be writing a mail to the Police commending then, but I am.  Well done! 

Best Regards, 

Nick 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-09 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sir/Madam, 

We cordially support you.  Hope the hard time will be over soon.  Proud of you all with my continuous support now and ever! 

Yours truly, 
 
Dr. Leung
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-08 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To Hong Kong Police, 

All of you are doing a terrific job to maintain the law and order of Hong Kong.
I fully support the Hong Kong Police Force.

Regards, 

Desiree
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-08 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force   </title><content>Dear all, 

We hope you'll stay calm and not get too upset.  The majority of the people in Hong Kong and all over the world can see what is happening, and understand your situation. We fully support Hong Kong Police!

We hope this situation will soon be over, and you will not be under the stress any more!  We are proud of you!

Best regards, 

Mr. LEE
A Hong Kong Citizen
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-08 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear ladies and gentlemen of the Hong Kong Police Force,

I am a retired person who had worked in the legal field for about 30 years.  As a retiree, I have been fortunate during the last 20 days of turmoil in our city as I did not have to go to work and did not need to be in any place at any particular time so my daily activities have not been really bothered by what have been happening in the streets.  

I have followed the news reports closely and I have personally been to a number of locations to observe what was taking place. 　

I now write to give you people my heartfelt thank to you for doing a very difficult job under tremendously difficult circumstances in a truly professional manner.  You have behaved with discipline and restraint in the face of much provocation and some seriously biased reports.  This is truly admirable.

Please be rest assured that there are people in Hong Kong who have observed, appreciated and supported your work for the last 20 days, and they will continue to do so.  Please take care when carrying out your duties. I am sure your families are proud of you and I am proud of our city's Police Force.

Yours truly,　

Agnes
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-07 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force   </title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,

I would like to write to you on behalf of my family and friends.  We want to tell you that we are very upset by what has happened in Hong Kong in the last few weeks. 

We can see that you are trying your utmost to maintain order and ensure that ordinary people can lead a normal life.  You have been very restrained, though you are constantly being challenged by some people who may or may not know what they are doing.

We must thank you, the members of the Police Force, for sticking to your duties, in spite of the harassment, insult and hardship!

Sincerely, 

Tony 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-07 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Sirs/Madam,

Thanks all of you for maintaining the law and order in Hong Kong and the security of our community impartially.  I am proud of all of you.  Although all of you have been facing an avalanche of stressful and backlog of works, and a lot of insulting and provocative criticisms from unlawful occupiers, you guys remain very calm to avoid violence against some lawless people.  All members of my family still 100% support Hong Kong Police. 

Best regards,

Mr. Wong 
Hong Kong permanent resident

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-07 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear Sir and Madam, 

Thank you so much for your contribution in maintaining law and order.  No other Police Forces in the world will have this level of tolerance, tact and empathy.  You ladies and gentlemen are only the enforcers, and protesters should not vent their anger on you.  A big salute to each and every one of you.  Carry on… you have many silent supporters.

Best regards, 

A group of Singaporeans working in Hong Kong

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-06 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Respected and honorable HK Police Force,
 
I am writing to express my sincerest appreciation and support to all men and women serving in HK Police Force on behalf of my family.
 
I am a very normal HK-born 40 year-old citizen, having a very normal life of committing myself for the betterment of my family as well as contributing to Hong Kong as a normal citizen.  With no relative working in the Police Force, I have been enjoying a safe society since my childhood with Police officers always in position whenever they are mostly needed.  Being a responsible man, I fully understand there will be imperfection but I trust HK Police as a whole who are always in place and in front of us all to battle against crime and evils in our world.
 
My support and contribution is very small of course as I am not famous to make public address or advertisements in news, but still I wish to write this to you all, before I leave my office today going back to my family, knowing HK is a safe society with HK Police’s devotion and commitment to protect all HK citizens.

Thank you, good health and salute to all officers.
 
Respectfully yours,

Shie
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-06 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force  </title><content>Dear all members of the HK Police,

On behalf of my family members, I wish to give our deepest gratitude for the hard work everyone of you has displayed in safeguarding us, as peace-loving Hong Kongers, against the ugly rogue-demonstrators.  You have shown to the world the highest professionalism and the greatest perseverance over this long and tiring struggle which rarely happens in HK.  We are proud of you and please keep up the spirit as you can be assured that the vast majority of Hong Kongers are behind you. Thank you and wish you all good luck and good health.

Best Regards, 

Leonard 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-06 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police Force, 

I am writing to express my sincere and heartfelt gratitude to all of your efforts in maintaining the law and order in HK during the Occupy Central social movement.  Your professionalism, your patience and your perseverance are highly praised.  We are proud to have you around! 

I believe all of you do support and comfort each other, do take good care of yourselves and your colleagues as well.  Tell yourselves that the violence will soon be over, have hope, and sustain to the end.  As a Hong Kong citizen, I totally support and trust the work of Hong Kong Police Force.  Your works are visible to us for the good of Hong Kong.  Hope this email can boost your spirit a bit.  We are with you and back you up with prayers and concerns!  Add oil Hong Kong Police Force!

Sincerely yours, 

Miriam 
A Hong Kong Citizen who supports HKPF
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-05 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>2014-11-05 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force 

Dear HK Police,

After all these days with terrible workload, great pressure and facing all kinds of ridiculous behaviours of the protesters, all the HK Police have demonstrated to the whole world their professionalism.  You have won our full respect and support!  HK people clearly see with our own eyes, with our hearts, and we all know the true story and understand what is going on.  You are not alone!  You have our full support!
Don't give up!  Seven million people count on you!

Best regards,

Julia 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force  </title><content>Dear all, 

I really appreciate the way of Police Force in handling the chaotic protest which happened outside Central Government Offices on 29 Sept.  Being a law enforcement agent, it is a difficult time, especially when decision has to be made in a spot.  Always support our Hong Kong Police Force!  You guys are doing right and doing well.

Best Regards, 

Ms. Leung.
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear all members of Hong Kong Police, 

The intelligent people saw what you all did.  Unbelievable courageous and efforts. We are all behind you.  Thank you!

Yours,

Kenneth  

</content></item><item><title>2014-11-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force</title><content>To all police officers in Hong Kong, 
 
Thank You!  I just want to do my part by sending a warmest appreciation to all of the hard working, disciplined and professional Police officers in Hong Kong, whom have worked tirelessly to ensure the safety of all citizens of Hong Kong including the protestors during this critical period.  Please take care of yourself and be safe while fulfilling your duties.  
 
Regards,

Sam
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear Hong Kong Police,   

Just a short message to show my support to Hong Kong Police as well as my thankfulness to all who have been working hard in the current chaos.  We are proud of you.  Well done and please keep up the good work.  Thank You! 

Yours, 

Joan 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear Sir/Madam,

I have been following the Occupy Central development from overseas recently and I would like to take this opportunity to say to you all: "what a fine job you guys have been performing!"  I believe the Hong Kong Police had always exercised impartial judgement during the rapidly elevating crisis situation.  The event erupted and escalated all in a sudden and law enforcers at the scene need to rely on experience to perform their duties in an instant.  I, from the bottom of my heart, want to say "thank you", thank you for upholding the law of Hong Kong and I pray that you guys will continue to fulfil your duties as the last defence of the sanity in Hong Kong.

Sincerely,

Tom
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-04 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force  </title><content>Dear Police Officers:

I appreciate all that you do for Hong Kong, especially in this week during Occupy Central.  I think you have done a good job and acted professionally during this Occupy Central movement.  You have my respect.  Tonight is going to be a very hard night.  Please add oil and be safe.

Sincerely,

Kay 
</content></item><item><title>2014-11-03 - Compliment on Hong Kong Police Force </title><content>Dear all,

I feel obliged to thank you all again and again after watching the news.  These rioters are ridiculous and the whole world and the whole Hong Kong can see.  Please keep up your good work!  What you see everyday is the worse.  There are many of us who are still extremely supportive of you.  Many thanks!

Best regards,

Tracy

</content></item></channel></rss>